export const state = {
  auth: {
    isAuthenticated: true,
    uid: `iiB9XLF95zXXTnDkG0luc2sgvh22`,
    loading: `SUCCESS`,
  },
  tags: {
    tagsIncludingDeleted: {
      "1926ww60kMmODntxvstd": {
        name: `Test Tag Forever`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 13 2022 16:26:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 13 2022 16:26:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ": {
        name: `Vue`,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:10 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:10 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod": {
        name: `JavaScript Docs`,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:10 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:10 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "9swD16I7e9S7p8cj2rAM": {
        name: `Chakra UI`,
        createdDate: `Sun May 29 2022 14:37:16 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Sun May 29 2022 14:37:16 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      B3NhLE1WE5w7wC0BGbub: {
        name: `Git`,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm: {
        name: `Interview Questions`,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      FRYJ5b4qDWps8Egl8mrw: {
        name: `New tag works!!!`,
        isDeleted: true,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 07 2022 19:54:12 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 23:16:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      HPGpTmMLX4iFKog2u5Rm: {
        name: `JavaScript Object`,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ISZSggUEy6bPvg4jlNjd: {
        name: `HTML`,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy: {
        name: `JavaScript Array`,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      KxYIVkAnI7lWJRbJMQvm: {
        name: `General Programming`,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY: {
        name: `CSS`,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Rfe3j22KJ7nh5UjVB2y4: {
        name: `Next.js`,
        createdDate: `Fri Jun 17 2022 13:27:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Fri Jun 17 2022 13:27:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      UQFZObstxz4gOWDWaxKo: {
        name: `Aa tag for testingasdf`,
        isDeleted: true,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 10:15:06 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 22:47:06 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      VEiy15IEyjnO0RbmH8FV: {
        name: `ECMAScript?`,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Xf92QQ7BHRe67htkGzcP: {
        name: `Terms`,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm: {
        name: `React Hooks`,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      dAwfSnqSbKz6Vca6ybOr: {
        name: `React Testing`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 01 2022 10:09:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 01 2022 10:09:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      e1lSpuuIdmovubAEkSMR: {
        name: `Koa`,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6: {
        name: `JavaScript`,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      jcosukteLxJC3SKg6STx: {
        name: `TypeScript`,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ktYuM92Bbqu35Rj6jENC: {
        name: `Test Tag`,
        isDeleted: true,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 23:16:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      lB4kjB6sFIRBff8RfS1G: {
        name: `JavaScript Code`,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU: {
        name: `React`,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      pM9S35qYvsjLjcmWQPZQ: {
        name: `ECMA-262`,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:07 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:07 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw: {
        name: `CSS Selector`,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:07 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:07 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      xdCIOZf3nYatSg0RLDky: {
        name: `New tag number 2`,
        isDeleted: true,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 07 2022 19:55:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 23:16:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL: {
        name: `React 18`,
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:07 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:16:07 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
    },
  },
  flashcards: {
    flashcardsIncludingDeleted: {
      "08XCO9G54cZwi5oVCzws": {
        front: `What does this expand out to\n\nx += 5;`,
        back: `x = x + 5;`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "0B9wGJg1xN0IycPUyvV4": {
        front: `How can you make a property a function?`,
        back: `const o = {\n  foo: function () {},\n  bar() {}\n}`,
        tags: [`HPGpTmMLX4iFKog2u5Rm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "0KyHfJRSx2xQYFOeJ10D": {
        front: `Using the useState hook, how do you compute the new state using the previous state?`,
        back: `You can pass a function to setState.\n\n// e.g. incrementing state\nsetState((prevCount) => prevCount + 1)`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "0OTqiEYBEgHfezxv0YSq": {
        front: `Does hydration block the browser from doing other work in React 18 with Suspense?`,
        back: `No. Hydrating content inside Suspense boundaries happens with tiny gaps in which the browser can handle events. This allows events to be handled immediately, and the browser doesn't appear stuck during a long hydration on a low-end device.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "0UedDmsGqjoWBI8tAXaX": {
        front: `Explain a getter.`,
        back: `The \`get\` syntax is a dynamically computed value.\n\nconst o = {\n  a: 'foo',\n  get b() {\n    if (this.a === 'foo') {\n      return 'bar';\n    }\n    return 'baz';\n  }\n}\n\no.b; // bar`,
        tags: [`HPGpTmMLX4iFKog2u5Rm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "0aTvKWk8h2Aqe7e5WRqe": {
        front: `What does React.createElement() return?`,
        back: `A JavaScript object.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 16:13:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 16:13:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "0ezG10Nkobi5iSJEWf9d": {
        front: `How can you import and use a SFC?`,
        back: `<script setup>\n// Note: default import\nimport Foo from './Foo.vue'\n</script>\n\n<template>\n  <Foo />\n</template>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "0qHQLWx95NlwY3tSzTa3": {
        front: `Testing\n\nLine breaks\n\nGrrr`,
        back: `back`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "1IzsMlxX7KZXnjzPqpbY": {
        front: `What does the acronym HTML stand for?`,
        back: `HTML = Hypertext Markup Language`,
        tags: [`ISZSggUEy6bPvg4jlNjd`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "1ZtrgiGNeuUC1DkcNXcy": {
        front: `What is a SFC?`,
        back: `Single-File Component. A Vue SFC encapsulates the component's logic (JavaScript), template (HTML), and styles (CSS) in a single file.\n\n<script>\n// some JavaScript\n</script>\n\n<template>\n  <!-- some HTML --->\n</template>\n\n<style scoped>\n/* some styles */\n</style>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "1hJj9UoBN6Wh3I4BkYYS": {
        front: `Boolean("");`,
        back: `false`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "1iotsUtcZbEkdZC5gevq": {
        front: `Explain get and set on computed()`,
        back: `const firstName = ref('John');\nconst lastName = ref('Doe');\n\nconst fullName = computed({\n  get() {\n    return firstName.value + ' ' + lastName.value\n  },\n  set(newValue) {\n    [firstName.value, lastName.value] = newValue.split(' ');\n  }\n});\n\nfullName = 'Josh Clyde'; // updates firstName and lastName`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Fri May 27 2022 19:05:22 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "1waimJMW0mrbJDTYrzky": {
        front: `"3" + 4 + 5;\n3 + 4 + "5";`,
        back: `// 345\n// 75`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "23qkSrdQ2U94Vtsve6ao": {
        front: `Where can JavaScript expressions be used in Vue templates?`,
        back: `• Inside text interpolations (mustache)\n• In the attribute value of any Vue directives (v-)`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "2DDI4XV9Jd2j3nGSIWlh": {
        front: `Explain the useInsertionEffect hook and the syntax.`,
        back: `useInsertionEffect(didUpdate);\n\nThis is a hook that allows CSS-in-JS libraries to address performance issues injecting styles in render. Unless I'm building a CSS-in-JS library, don't expect to ever use this.`,
        tags: [`bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "2Sp0I2rRBEKbm7915fpD": {
        front: `How does a box with an outer display type of \`block\` behave?`,
        back: `• The box will break onto a new line\n• The box will extend in the inline direction to fill the space available in its container (most of the time, that means 100% of the space available)\n• The \`width\` and \`height\` properties are respected\n• Padding, margin and border will cause other elements to be pushed away from the box`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "2TPTqaQnyCPfNLmDD44D": {
        front: `How can you merge 2 different arrays?`,
        back: `const arr1 = [1, 2, 3];\nconst arr2 = [4, 5, 6];\nconst arr3 = arr1.concat(arr2); // [1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6]`,
        tags: [`iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`, `JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "2n3liFnrsxfI4Lv1ktC9": {
        front: `RFC`,
        back: `Request for Comments. A publication of something (in the programming world probably some technical specifications) meant for community discussion.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `Xf92QQ7BHRe67htkGzcP`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "2u4sCQHU5McuFXviwOnH": {
        front: `Which edition of ECMAScript was not published?`,
        back: `The fourth edition.`,
        tags: [`pM9S35qYvsjLjcmWQPZQ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "37woBGMH0WQiLuS5BAeS": {
        front: `How can you access the DOM state in a watcher callback after Vue has updated it?`,
        back: `watch(source, callback, { flush: 'post'});\nwatchEffect(callback, { flush: 'post' });\nwatchPostEffect(callback);`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "49crG2Ouvd2HU8I75oK3": {
        front: `isFinite(NaN);`,
        back: `false`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "4ATMPHJZTCkWHEuB2BZd": {
        front: `Explain flatMap`,
        back: `// Is same as doing map then flat on an array\n// Can allow a nice way to either add or remove elements when mapping\nconst arr = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5];\narr.flatMap(x => x < 3 ? [] : [x + 1]); // [4, 5, 6]\narr.flatMap(x => x < 3 ? [x, x] : [x]); // [1, 1, 2, 2, 3, 4, 5]`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "4fFJE4Bu09ksCn55t8L5": {
        front: `Boolean(undefined);`,
        back: `false`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "4lEt5Nc5NgryPmSjrcE3": {
        front: `A JavaScript runtime`,
        back: `The environment in which the JavaScript code runs and is interpreted by a JavaScript engine. The runtime provides the host objects that JavaScript can operate on and work with.`,
        tags: [`VEiy15IEyjnO0RbmH8FV`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "4rOkDl7D3ssN2d8sCuwv": {
        front: `How can you dynamically toggle classes?`,
        back: `<div :class="{ active: isActive }"></div>\n\nThe above means the presence of the \`active\` class will be determined by the truthiness of \`isActive\`.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "4ukOWBMXOEUzElIHrkUh": {
        front: `let x = 3;\ny = x++;\n\nWhat is x and y?`,
        back: `// x = 4\n// y = 3`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "503vsyrLfo6JPm9AnGJE": {
        front: `How does Koa middleware cascade?`,
        back: `Using async functions, Koa goes downstream and then control flows back upstream.\n\nBasically, you'll provide middleware to your Koa application in some order. Each request will flow through these middleware, starting at the first. The first middleware can perform behavior it needs to, and then when it's done can invoke the next middleware. Then the next middleware can do its stuff, and on and on. While moving from middleware to middleware, each one will be saved in a stack-like manner. After there are no more middleware to execute downstream, the stack will unwind and each middleware is resumed to perform and additional behavior it wants.`,
        tags: [`e1lSpuuIdmovubAEkSMR`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "5B417tyRhHlwI6yIWXn5": {
        front: `How can you determine whether an array includes a certain value?`,
        back: `const arr = [1, 2, 3];\narr.includes(2); // true\narr.includes(4); // false`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "5TKYGbbhBGsd1YnbRl6B": {
        front: `When is useReducer usually preferable to useState?`,
        back: `When you have complex state logic that involves multiple sub-values or when the next state depends on the previous one.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "5V8oqXC4ya4aItgCopjz": {
        front: `What are the two built-in numeric types?`,
        back: `Number and BigInt`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "5ZCasGW2iZSKoKYtQlVq": {
        front: `Loop over array`,
        back: `const arr = [1, 2, 3];\narr.forEach(x => console.log(x));`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "5hrsF5NQEU6Dgh2eCC1f": {
        front: `Explain \`watchEffect()\``,
        back: `Runs a function immediately while reactively tracking its dependencies and re-runs it whenever the dependencies are changed.\n\nconst count = ref(0);\nwatchEffect(() => console.log(count.value));\n// logs 0\n\ncount.value++;\n// logs 1`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "604OztA7sPg45ngiLvnv": {
        front: `What is Vue?`,
        back: `Vue is a JavaScript framework for building interfaces. It builds on top of standard HTMl, CSS and JavaScript, and provides a declarative and component-based programming model that helps you efficiently develop user interfaces.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "65d4eiB5gj3tqzADjZLS": {
        front: `What is Reactivity?`,
        back: `Vue automatically tracks JavaScript state changes and efficiently updates the DOM when changes happen.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "69Lj8FuXDXilFcxqHtvl": {
        front: `Explain the v-show directive`,
        back: `Toggle the element's visibility based on the truthy-ness of the expression value.\n\nWill always be rendered and remain in the DOM, but toggles the \`display\` CSS property.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "6CTNUQxAEPaePDMxb9Fs": {
        front: `Descendant Combinator/Selector`,
        back: `Combines two selectors that elements matched by the second selector are selected if they have an ancestor (parent, parent's parent, parent's parent's parent, etc.) element matching the first selector.\n\nselector1 selector2 {\n  color: green;\n}`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "6FFXLObvdHPEdz05o3aJ": {
        front: `Are all properties and methods of Math static?`,
        back: `Yes`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "6L62Ld26x3nHlFndyi5e": {
        front: `Where are defineProps and defineEmits able to be used?`,
        back: `Only usable inside <script setup>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "6N27zIa9NSangBpjl8fl": {
        front: `What's the equivalent of a React fragment in Vue?`,
        back: `<template>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "6ex2PTfKgFKwbNyb4Uep": {
        front: `How can you copy part of an array to another location in the same array?`,
        back: `const arr = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5];\narr.copyWithin(0, 3, 4); // [4, 2, 3, 4, 5]\narr.copyWithin(0, 3); // [4, 5, 3, 4, 5]\n\nReturns a new array, does not mutate.\nReplaces the element in the target index.`,
        tags: [`iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`, `JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "6lBjglJfS59AMuMVnstN": {
        front: `Who maintains the CSS specifications?`,
        back: `A group called the CSS Working Group, a group within the W3C.\n\n(?) But just because new specifications have been added does not mean browsers support it. That's up to the browser to implement.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "73bdyrAiVSdB88VS5Y5V": {
        front: `Try again`,
        back: `Please work`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "75pzujJeS73jeCC8M8H0": {
        front: `Explain the v-html directive`,
        back: `Updates the element's innerHTML. Contents of v-html are inserted as plain HTML.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "76joC4iJ7boAJVLkKlSq": {
        front: `What is an urgent update?`,
        back: `Reflect direct interaction, like typing, clicking, pressing, and so on.`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "7EMsnn6OSvyZpJ9i7Rxg": {
        front: `How can you access the last element of an array?`,
        back: `const arr = [1, 2, 3];\narr.at(-1); // 3 (preferred)\narr[arr.length - 1]; // 3\n`,
        tags: [`iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`, `JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "7Ny1uzvfd7tiRQWCpzPh": {
        front: `Is it okay to assign or destructure a reactive object's property into a local variable?`,
        back: `No. Vue's reactivty tracking works over property access, so we must always keep the same reference to the reactive object.\n\nconst state = reactive({ count: 0 });\nlet n = state.count; // bad, n is disconnected from state.count\nn++; // does not affect original state\nlet { count } = state; // bad\ncount++; // does not affect original state\n\n// function receives a plain number and\n// cannot track changes to state.count\ncallSomeFunction(state.count); `,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "7Y1cbPjRvN19ZFyrkMC8": {
        front: `NaN + 5;`,
        back: `NaN`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "7bORBqVlHQw5vDTnp03R": {
        front: `How should you display filtered/sorted results of an array?`,
        back: `Create a computed property.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "7cnpslax9ultB1HDMdSp": {
        front: `Explain the v-slot directive.`,
        back: `Denote named slots or slots that expect to receive props.\n\nLimited to\n• <template>\n• components\n\n<SomeComponent>\n  <template v-slot=something>\n     foo\n  </template>\n</SomeComponent>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "7fXzCClAwDxt8DjfapAF": {
        front: `When can Concurrent React cause issues with libraries?`,
        back: `Generally, libraries which deal with data fetching, state management, or styling because these libraries store their own state outside of React.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "7lPkJaIrSF8CrpYz8rvG": {
        front: `How does the JavaScript event loop work?`,
        back: `JavaScript is single threaded. The way code works is that one piece of code (?) runs at a time. JavaScript then has this queue of messages that need to be run, and when the current piece of code finishes then it'll pop the next message off the queue and run that.`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "7qPc3dd4y6YldEVfagwp": {
        front: `Give an example of tearing not being an issue before React 18 and why it's an issue with React 18.`,
        back: `This is my current understanding, however I'm not 100% confident on this yet.\n\nBasically, before React 18 rendering is synchronous and occurs all at once, so let's say I change a color from blue to red then it won't have an effect until after the current render has fully finished and the next render changes all components to red.\n\nBut in React 18, with concurrency React can pause a render, do something else, then continue the render. So if a render is paused when changing the color from blue to red then any components rendered after the pause will be red, but before the pause will be blue.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "84rD9t7GtDJdhYUFxjYI": {
        front: `What are the different ways you can integrate CSS into a webpage?`,
        back: `An external stylesheet, an internal stylesheet, and with inline styles.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "879MJ6HSbAQ9UdLD7aNV": {
        front: `When were async functions introduced?`,
        back: `ECMAScript 2017. Promises were introduced in 2015, async functions in 2017.`,
        tags: [`pM9S35qYvsjLjcmWQPZQ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "8I6ov72gP3pnjodpTR1Q": {
        front: `What happens when you pass a class attribute to a component with a single root element?`,
        back: `Those classes will be added to the component's root element and merged with any existing classes already on it.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "8ZihunQWB8xddIh8elLJ": {
        front: `How many parameters can a getter have?`,
        back: `Zero.`,
        tags: [`HPGpTmMLX4iFKog2u5Rm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "8xooqSQsyCU7zrmEu3dL": {
        front: `What does CSS stand for?`,
        back: `Cascading Style Sheets`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "8xz1mQPWAFgEw5ATasoI": {
        front: `Explain the useState hook and the syntax.`,
        back: `const [state, setState] = useState(initialState);\n\nReturns a stateful value and a function to update it.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:24:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "8ygr6cyvpk06u2XL2xZO": {
        front: `What does react-dom/server do?`,
        back: `The ReactDOMServer object enables you to render components to static markup. Typically, it's used on a Node server.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "97Qq8xrYy1uxzSMLf9J9": {
        front: `The ___ method executes a user supplied "reducer" callback function on each element of the array, in order, passing in the return value from the calculation on the preceding element. The final result is a single value.\n\nThe first time that the callback is run there is no "return value of the previous calculation". If supplied, an initial value may be used in its place. Otherwise the array element at index 0 is used as the initial value and iteration starts from the next element (index 1 instead of index 0).`,
        back: `const arr = [1, 2, 3];\narr.reduce((acc, x) => acc + x) // 6\narr.reduce((acc, x) => acc + x, 10) // 16`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "97nSjVb8ejQ0YrtPMb9K": {
        front: `How can you prevent the default in an event handler?`,
        back: `function handleEvent(e) {\n    e.preventDefault();\n  }`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Thu Jun 16 2022 14:54:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Thu Jun 16 2022 14:54:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "9GfYQx4wcF517bGgPV4D": {
        front: `What is this equivalent too? Is this recommended?\n\n<Foo bar />`,
        back: `<Foo bar={true} />\n\nIn general, we don’t recommend not passing a value for a prop, because it can be confused with the ES6 object shorthand {foo} which is short for {foo: foo} rather than {foo: true}. This behavior is just there so that it matches the behavior of HTML.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 17:09:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 17:09:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "9SGpJPtKkmsHGXdCDhhM": {
        front: `What is a transition?`,
        back: `A new concept in React to distinguish between urgent and non-urgent updates.`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "9avxzwyW43oVG5aY0ooT": {
        front: `What happens when passing an array to multiple checkbox's v-model?`,
        back: `The array will always contain the value attribute from each of the currently checked boxes.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "9bst68DX15XLFmtEX1fR": {
        front: `What have I done to keep up to date with the programming world?`,
        back: `Reading documentation on websites. React, Vue. Following blogs.`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "9liIUNT36eo0TFd74hpw": {
        front: `How can you stop a \`watchEffect\` watcher?`,
        back: `const stop = watchEffect(() => {});\nstop();`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "9x2M8YegocZpR3hPzAsY": {
        front: `Why is there a \`react\` package and multiple other react related packages?`,
        back: `Ideally, the \`react\` package has nothing to do with a web browser. Other packages (such as react-dom/client) is the glue to connect a React element to the browser.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "9zIdG61bc6lhtuA1TYf7": {
        front: `What happens if you access an element in an array with an index outside of its length?`,
        back: `You will get undefined. No error is thrown.\n\nconst arr = [1, 2, 3];\narr[100]; // undefined`,
        tags: [`iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`, `JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      A38jkcu407MsOQZGvXYE: {
        front: `Test 2!`,
        back: `Test 2!!`,
        tags: [`1926ww60kMmODntxvstd`],
        isDeleted: true,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 13 2022 16:26:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 13 2022 16:28:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ACJaYPj3uH4SMM2S5Mt3: {
        front: `How can you access props?`,
        back: `// in script setup\nconst props = defineProps<{ foo: string; }>()\n\n// in template\n<div>{{ foo }} </div>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      AYCI3QvhVBBNtA8qapbV: {
        front: `Attribute Selector whose value can be exactly \`value\` or can begin with \`value\` immediately followed by a hyphen "-"\n\nOften used for language subcode matches.`,
        back: `[attr|=value]`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      AdRUHA2B52MVuZU3Xgkj: {
        front: `Selector List`,
        back: `Selects all the matching nodes\n\nspan, div {\n  color: green;\n}\n\nEdge case: If one selector within the list is invalid then it will invalidate the whole rule`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Ahm7TeSIqI7ONpoXoVfM: {
        front: `Compare React hooks with Vue Composition API`,
        back: `In the Composition API,\n• The \`setup\` code is run only once.\n• Vue's runtime reactivity system automatically collects reactive dependencies used in computed properties and watchers, so there's no need to manually declare dependencies\n• No need to manually cache callback functions to avoid unnecessary child updates. In general, Vue knows when to update children\n\nWhen using React hooks,\n• Hooks are call-order sensitive and cannot be conditional\n• TLDR dependencies array can be annoying`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Ai09VIyfjVgJK1AvgzmG: {
        front: `What are the 2 major SSR features in React 18 unlocked by Suspense?`,
        back: `• Streaming HTML on the server\n• Selective Hydration on the client`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      AsAeOZNbt1QxLoMiIfoj: {
        front: `What's the Margin box?`,
        back: `The Margin box is the outermost layer, wrapping the Content box, Padding box and the Border box. Serves as whitespace between this element and other elements. Can be controlled using \`margin\` and other related properties.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Ayg3BcZmlFWkM1PxeCV4: {
        front: `Explain isReadonly()`,
        back: `Checks if an object is a proxy created by readonly() or shallowReadonly()`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      BBkj355rixxP0YoWahJl: {
        front: `Can components return undefined?`,
        back: `As of React 18, components can now render undefined without any warnings.`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      BDhunSIg2wXWT8PcMn8b: {
        front: `Explain the v-bind directive`,
        back: `The v-bind directive instructs Vue to keep the an element's attribute in sync with some JavaScript value.\n\n// dynamicId is some JavaScript variable\n<div v-bind:id="dynamicId"></div>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      BDiFSgyBD3nf0PhehlcF: {
        front: `Tell me about a time you had to quickly adjust your work priorities to meet changing demands.`,
        back: `Maybe functional tests`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      BDwvYS2QP4FbnXV4H1lU: {
        front: `What is a CSS declaration?`,
        back: `When a property is paired with a value.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      BIzrABvbKliS58w0aCWH: {
        front: `What does Hypertext Markup Language mean?`,
        back: `Hypertext refers to links that connect web pages to one another. \\n The prefix “hyper” means “above” or “beyond”.Markup is derived from the “marking up” of paper manuscripts. Markup refers to data which is distinct from the document’s content that is typically not displayed to end users. A markup language is a set of rules governing what markup information may be included in a document and how it is combined with the content of the document in a way to facilitate use by humans and computer programs.`,
        tags: [`ISZSggUEy6bPvg4jlNjd`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      BMIbbN2lbNLkYGexhgaW: {
        front: `What is the Math built-in object?`,
        back: `An object that has properties and methods for mathematical constants and functions.`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      BQg8RauOKCfz7kb0zIvL: {
        front: `Simplicity`,
        back: `Strive to keep the component API fairly simple and show real world scenarios of using the component.`,
        tags: [`9swD16I7e9S7p8cj2rAM`],
        createdDate: `Sun May 29 2022 15:08:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Sun May 29 2022 15:08:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      BSPoIFWZj2qcHF8vLQqX: {
        front: `Why is it a good idea to generally set tuples to be readonly?`,
        back: `Tuples tend to be created and left un-modified in most code.`,
        tags: [`jcosukteLxJC3SKg6STx`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 13:14:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 13:14:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      BTHKMpFiSdxCy8hPrNqM: {
        front: `What's the Border box?`,
        back: `The Border box wraps the Content box and the Padding box. Can be controlled using the \`border\` and related properties.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Bza6esoBxVqVNkcie6e8: {
        front: `What is the rest parameter syntax?`,
        back: `Allows a function to accept an indefinite number of arguments as an array.\n\nMust be the last parameter and can only have one.\n\nfunction foo(a, b, ...theArgs) {\n\n}`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      C0Zwaw2ft2IsAHfkjTd3: {
        front: `Do you prefer working independently or on a team?`,
        back: `Both. It's important to me to have teammates to rely on and collaborate with. As well as be inspired with how driven and passionate they are. But when coding a solution sometimes it's do it independently.`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      C81PgeD0Yd0woq6XnHDH: {
        front: `Testing this!!`,
        back: `woowowow`,
        tags: [`UQFZObstxz4gOWDWaxKo`, `ktYuM92Bbqu35Rj6jENC`],
        createdDate: `Fri May 27 2022 11:20:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Fri May 27 2022 11:20:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      CIReK7HVQJNs09ASKRCS: {
        front: `How can you access object properties?`,
        back: `const obj = { foo: 'bar' };\nobj.foo; // bar\nobj['foo']; // bar`,
        tags: [`HPGpTmMLX4iFKog2u5Rm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      CXd7CzFtobpFstbhlJnS: {
        front: `Commit sentence?`,
        back: `If applied, this commit will...`,
        tags: [`B3NhLE1WE5w7wC0BGbub`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      CcIgWA8HpCiLb0W3c3Jo: {
        front: `How to write a CSS comment?`,
        back: `/* Hello there */`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Ce3PY8hQKEqYIdxTbLfU: {
        front: `What's the difference between function scope and block scope?`,
        back: `Function level scope restricted within the function, block scope restricted within a block.`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      CeURhbJMtpOI47WsIMXJ: {
        front: `The ___ method reverses an array.`,
        back: `// reverse()\nconst arr = [1, 2, 3, 4];\narr.reverse(); // Mutates arr to be [4, 3, 2, 1]`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      CjX10rm5OcsWh6KS5Ol4: {
        front: `What is a CSS declaration block?`,
        back: `A grouping of multiple CSS declarations.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Ck3v4FWvXZveIr66fzij: {
        front: `Why am I looking for a job now?`,
        back: `I need a job and would to like to work for a company that has a passionate, driven environment.`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Cz6ejbRERcHEW77S9P09: {
        front: `Can you call functions inside a binding expression?`,
        back: `Yes.\n\nFunctions called inside binding expressions will be called every time the component updates, so they should not have any side effects (e.g. changing data)`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      D0ef86druiWAKOyy5GpV: {
        front: `Why are defineProps and defineEmits compiler macros?`,
        back: `They are compiled away when <script setup> is processed.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      D2VHesWO0RtfA56V1oHp: {
        front: `What is an inline-block?`,
        back: `Middle ground between inline and block. The element will not break onto a new line (like inline) but it will respect the width and height attributes (like block) and can vertically push away elements with padding, margin and border (like block. inline can only push away elements horizontally).`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      DW7Quj75lojilWtIs5um: {
        front: `How can you make a getter with a computed property name?`,
        back: `const a = 'foo';\nconst o = {\n  get [a]() { return 'bar'; }\n};\nobj.foo; // bar`,
        tags: [`HPGpTmMLX4iFKog2u5Rm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      DhI28sQvnefxvmcDatj5: {
        front: `Do you know how closures work?`,
        back: `Yes. When creating a JavaScript function, a "closure" is created. Basically there's like this scope within the function that things outside the function cannot access, but within the function can.`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      DjymydcM0fAuQ6EgweJ7: {
        front: `How can a Vue component render content passed to it?`,
        back: `<slot />`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      DmMsNhSSLVISt68YBAdF: {
        front: `How can you declare a tuple with an optional property.`,
        back: `By writing out a question mark after an element's type. Optional tuple elements can only come at the end, and also affect the type of length.\n\ntype Either2dOr3d = [number, number, number?];`,
        tags: [`jcosukteLxJC3SKg6STx`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 13:09:06 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 13:09:06 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      DosiD3Gt1xL37cJkTSmL: {
        front: `When is a component considered mounted?`,
        back: `• After all of its synchronous child components have been mounted (does not include async components or <Suspense> trees)\n• Its own DOM tree has been created and inserted into the parent container. Note it only guarantees that the component's DOM tree is in-document if the application's root container is also in-document.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      DpLFBbUrs71KF63HGRgc: {
        front: `How can you get an element from an array?`,
        back: `const arr = ['foo', 'bar', 'baz'];\n\narr[0]; // foo\narr.at(0); // foo\narr.at(-1); // baz`,
        tags: [`iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`, `JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      DpY0vjykHX99mbxb05o3: {
        front: `What's the difference between let, const and var?`,
        back: `let: block-level variable that can be changed\n\nconst: block-level variable that cannot be changed\n\nvar: function-level variable that can be changed`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      E5Zrxar7BENXC676nSez: {
        front: `What's the Content box?`,
        back: `The area where your content is displayed. Can be sized using properties like \`width\` and \`height\`.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      EOY5Tn0yhpqmeRsKV2AM: {
        front: `STAR`,
        back: `Situational - Describe the situation where everything happened.\n\nTask - Describe the task you had to complete in order to solve the problem/issue at hand.\n\nAction - Explain what actions you took to complete the task.\n\nResults - Talk about the results of your action and try to be as detailed as possible. How did your actions lead to the company or organization to function better?`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      EQMJnmAA5prbjp0JpXL3: {
        front: `Attribute Selector whose value is prefixed by \`value\``,
        back: `[attr^=value]`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      EYpGtN7wXQ1hYNDOZd5b: {
        front: `Explain the v-for directive`,
        back: `Render the element or template block multiple times based on the source data.\n\n<div v-for="item in items">\n  {{ item.text }}\n</div>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      EcdNjf2pT8bxbPq8HOpO: {
        front: `What is a React element?`,
        back: `An element is a plain object describing a component instance or DOM node and its desired properties. It contains only information about the component type, its properties, and any child elements inside it.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 16:53:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 16:53:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      EgLGTdOOylCs761BWShw: {
        front: `Explain the useRef hook and the syntax.`,
        back: `const refContainer = useRef(initialValue);\n\nuseRef returns a mutable ref object whose .current property is initialized to the passed argument (initialValue). The returned object will persist for the full lifetime of the component.`,
        tags: [`bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      EkfGRsowiFbXPPXGmjnV: {
        front: `When does the ref attribute set the value of the corresponding variable?`,
        back: `After the component is mounted.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      EtCRIY3mCdVLnJJ9gVEU: {
        front: `What was ECMAScript originally designed to be? What is it now?`,
        back: `Originally a Web scripting language. Now is a general-purpose programming language.`,
        tags: [`pM9S35qYvsjLjcmWQPZQ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      F0DSdgycvairJg65G3NR: {
        front: `What's the difference between unit, integration, functional and E2E tests?`,
        back: `Unit tests are typically testing a specific piece of code.\nIntegration and functional???\n`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      F1rdp3F63qzbHezCGw05: {
        front: `What is Concurrent React?`,
        back: `A new behind-the-scenes mechanism that enables React to prepare multiple versions of your UI at the same time.`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      F3gCU2u9olKFPyPj85ol: {
        front: `What format is a Number?`,
        back: `Double-precision floating-point format, which is a computer number format usually occupying 64 bits in computer memory.`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      F6twCJwYOxmA8RRcybW8: {
        front: `How is specificity calculated in CSS?`,
        back: `Specificity is measured using 4 different values, 4 single digits in 4 columns.\n\n1. Thousands: Score one in the column when the style is inline\n2. Hundreds: Score one for each ID selector in the overall selector\n3. Tens: Score one for each class selector, attribute selector, or pseudo-class in the overall selector\n4. Ones: Score one for each element selector or pseudo-element in the overall selector`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      F7jI6bKhrxXxmiqK7w3W: {
        front: `When was the fifth edition adopted?`,
        back: `2009`,
        tags: [`pM9S35qYvsjLjcmWQPZQ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      F9NQVUrTAQDmS172AImD: {
        front: `What happens when you give false, null, undefined and true as a child?`,
        back: `They are valid, but simply do not render.\n\nThat is why you can conditionally render React elements doing something like  {shouldRender && <Foo />}. However, some falsy values like 0 are still rendered by React, so make sure the expression before && is always boolean.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 17:15:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 17:15:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      FC853sNlZAFOrBhxBVZG: {
        front: `Boolean(NaN);`,
        back: `false`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      FHA4nmG7JGYFflVbZf49: {
        front: `Why should you not destructure the \`props\` object?`,
        back: `The \`props\` object is reactive. If destructured, the destructed variables will lose reactivity. So always access props in the form of \`props.foo\`.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      FMYE5tAD71LjQ53wWEYH: {
        front: `Type selector`,
        back: `Matches elements by node name\n\nAll the <a> elements\na {\n  color: red;\n}`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      FhaiQOGVCPQdFpyF55hP: {
        front: `What does "specificity" mean in CSS?`,
        back: `It's how the browser decides which rule applies if multiple rules with different selectors apply to the same element.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Fp3ow41P23Yx0HeIZKX9: {
        front: `Explain isReactive()`,
        back: `Checks if an object is a proxy created by reactive() or shallowReactive()`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      GNAvkVVFOunpLrQlfMNm: {
        front: `What's an example that I have ran into where useReducer was a better use case than useState?`,
        back: `My state values were month and year. I needed to increment and decrement them together by month, and whether or not year was incremented/decremented depended on the month value.`,
        tags: [`bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`],
        createdDate: `Mon Jun 06 2022 01:29:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Mon Jun 06 2022 01:29:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      GOQ2iaMl8XTXbwXfbW6Z: {
        front: `What 2 languages were ECMAScript based on?`,
        back: `JavaScript and JScript`,
        tags: [`VEiy15IEyjnO0RbmH8FV`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      GVF5dmLM68CUJLYnUcE5: {
        front: `What is margin collapsing?`,
        back: `If two elements whose margins touch, and both margins are positive, those margins will combine to become one margin, and its size will be equal to the largest individual margin.\n\nIf one margin is negative, it will be subtracted from the total. When both are negative, the margins will collapse and the furthest from zero will be used.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      GZ2e20NTUFOcW9Zf77mn: {
        front: `The ___ method test whether at least one element in the array passes the test implemented by the provided function.`,
        back: `const arr = [1, 2, 3];\narr.some(x => x > 1); // true\narr.some(x => x > 4); // false\n[].some(x => true); // false`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      GiI3vQUIBU2PDqRXCwuu: {
        front: `What is a JavaScript expression?`,
        back: `An expression is any valid unit of code that resolves to a value.`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 15:59:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 15:59:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      GsFIPGMzJvi35kIeeUbK: {
        front: `Can directive arguments use a JavaScript expression?`,
        back: `Yes.\n\n<a :[attributeName]="url">...</a>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      HArJ4JImN6Iqz9quxRlI: {
        front: `Explain \`ref()\``,
        back: `Takes an inner value and returns a reactive and mutable ref object, which has a single property \`.value\` that points to the inner value.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Ha8eE5baNdrBP917ngzm: {
        front: `How can you clean up resources that a useEffect hook may have created?`,
        back: `The effectful callback passed to useEffect can return a function that will be run before the component is removed from the UI. Additionally, when a component is rendered multiple times, the previous effect is cleaned up before executing the next effect.\n\nuseEffect(() => {\n  // some effectful stuff\n  return () => {\n    // clean up anything\n  }\n});`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      HcmqfnXyxCvqDEZW3sh5: {
        front: `What is !important?`,
        back: `Makes a particular property the most specific, overriding the normal rules of cascade.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      HdC5fOHrVlLweSnbenOJ: {
        front: `Boolean(0);`,
        back: `false`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      I1MwpyJh6yHPlKdpmmUe: {
        front: `Do defineProps and defineEmits need to be imported?`,
        back: `No.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      I3HTi0rGudvPkeexgNBL: {
        front: `Naming Props`,
        back: `Generally, ensure a prop name is indicative of what it does. Boolean props should be named using auxiliary verbs such as does, has, is and should.`,
        tags: [`9swD16I7e9S7p8cj2rAM`],
        createdDate: `Sun May 29 2022 15:11:05 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Sun May 29 2022 15:11:05 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      I5Q4NmNvHt5UaL9zRhpX: {
        front: `How does React solve the SSR problem of "You have to fetch everything before you can show anything"?`,
        back: `The Suspense component.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      IMNOmTg0r0JrS2wxvqq8: {
        front: `Explain the useCallback hook and the syntax.`,
        back: `const memoizedCallback = useCallback(\n  () => {\n    doSomething(a, b);\n  },\n  [a, b], // dependency array\n);\n\nReturns a memoized callback that only changes if one of the dependencies has changed.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      INrR1awLPLBK8ZUZ0QoY: {
        front: `Explain the useReducer hook and the syntax.`,
        back: `const [state, dispatch] = useReducer(reducer, initialState);\nconst [state, dispatch] = useReducer(reducer, initialArg, init);\n\nAn alternative to useState. Accepts a reducer of type (state, action) => newState, and returns the current state paired with a dispatch method.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      IbjRKurC2DoYECAKd04Q: {
        front: `Which HTML elements are empty?`,
        back: `img, input, link,\n\narea, base, br, col, embed, hr, keygen, meta, param, source, track, wbr\n`,
        tags: [`ISZSggUEy6bPvg4jlNjd`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      J6UtspSY6EETQsdSDk4C: {
        front: `What keywords declare new variables?`,
        back: `let, const, var`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      J74l4HLHHvegE9qsN4Q8: {
        front: `Composition`,
        back: `Break down components into smaller parts with minimal props to keep complexity low, and compose them together. This will ensure that the styles and functionality are flexible and extensible.`,
        tags: [`9swD16I7e9S7p8cj2rAM`],
        createdDate: `Sun May 29 2022 15:09:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Sun May 29 2022 15:09:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      JTzDVYIUv9Ry7UizDiLS: {
        front: `Number.isNan(NaN);`,
        back: `true`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      JgqAhRzgCsIZxJkuoezx: {
        front: `If needed, how can you destructure props?`,
        back: `\`toRefs()\` and \`toRef()\`\n\nconst { title } = toRefs(props);\nconst title = toRef(props, 'title');`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      JwptsWGVv982Nyh56VYR: {
        front: `What are some tradeoffs to consider when choosing testing tools?`,
        back: `Iteration speed vs Realistic environment.\n\nHow much to mock`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `dAwfSnqSbKz6Vca6ybOr`],
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 01 2022 10:11:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 01 2022 10:11:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      KFRBqMxZZxwdJiuPyFHQ: {
        front: `What is Koa?`,
        back: `A web framework designed by the team behind Express, which aims to be a smaller, more expressive, and more robust foundation for web applications and APIs.\n\nBy leveraging async functions, Koa allows you to ditch callbacks and greatly increase error-handling.\n\nKoa does not bundle any middleware within its core, and it provides an elegant suite of methods that make writing servers fast and enjoyable.`,
        tags: [`e1lSpuuIdmovubAEkSMR`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      KXG1eEYYRvBQmoDwmKML: {
        front: `When not using a build step, how can you define a Vue component?`,
        back: `As a plain JavaScript object.\n\nimport { ref } from 'vue';\n\nexport default {\n  setup() {\n    const count = ref(0);\n    return { count };\n  },\n  template: \`\n    <button @click="count++">\n      You clicked me {{ count }} times.\n    </button>\`\n}`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Kp6QQiMoOp0HLifaTLZr: {
        front: `How can you get the first element in an array that satisfy some condition?`,
        back: `const arr = [1, 2, 3];\narr.find(x => x > 1); // 2\narr.find(x => x > 4); // undefined`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      LAL62vpqogTERTlkdlhR: {
        front: `Explain \`isRef()\``,
        back: `Checks if a value is a ref object.\n\nlet foo: unknown\nif (isRef(foo)) {\n  // foo's type is narrowed to Ref<unknown>\n  foo.value\n}`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      LNZpmKjtIoxBoOPYVhAQ: {
        front: `Hey there.\n\nHello there.`,
        back: `What is up.\n\nNot much dude.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      LgoaEZlK64C2yCW9Lzs9: {
        front: `test 4`,
        back: `test 4`,
        tags: [`1926ww60kMmODntxvstd`],
        isDeleted: true,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 13 2022 17:30:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 13 2022 17:31:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      M6SPNBhPw1g5EnjXOEZT: {
        front: `Write a function that mutates some reactive state`,
        back: `const state = reactive({ count: 0 });\nfunction increment() {\n  state.count++;\n}`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      MCGR7rgDY8U5lUl5ceec: {
        front: `javascript flashcard front`,
        back: `javascript flashcard back`,
        tags: [`iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      MNbQd3bEJSI98lHbXhCw: {
        front: `How can you test whether all elements in an array meet some criteria?`,
        back: `const arr = [1, 2, 3];\narr.every(x => x < 10); // true\narr.every(x => x > 2); // false\n\n// If the array is empty, will always return true\n[].every(() => false); // true\n\n// Empty elements are skipped over\n[,,,].every(() => false); // true`,
        tags: [`iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`, `JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      MNwTF6hX2F60ZFJx5emZ: {
        front: `How can you bind a JavaScript object with multiple attributes to an element?`,
        back: `const obj = { id: 'container', class: 'wrapper' };\n\n<div v-bind="obj"></div>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      MS3WqxgUYHk8fVoOwxwA: {
        front: `What is Batching?`,
        back: `Batching is when React groups multiple state updates into a single re-render for better performance.`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      MUdlqFGMmEPyQzFvglhD: {
        front: `test 3`,
        back: `test 3`,
        tags: [`1926ww60kMmODntxvstd`],
        isDeleted: true,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 13 2022 17:30:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 13 2022 17:31:20 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      MXH6Vhpwmgt4Qi2WXjeZ: {
        front: `What does a browser do when encountering CSS it does not recognize?`,
        back: `Nothing. The browser ignores the CSS and moves on.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      MgDoBifHpmQe7imkhOjo: {
        front: `What are some of the problems with SSR that React 18 is trying to fix?`,
        back: `• You have to fetch everything before you can show anything (you have to collect all the data on the server before you can start sending any HTML to the client)\n• You have to load everything before you can hydrate anything\n• You have to hydrate everything before you can interact with anything`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      NBAtwIbueE0ToJq1UdOO: {
        front: `What is Composition API?`,
        back: `With Composition API, we define a component's logic using imported API functions, typically used with \`<script setup>\`.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      NQSY3eqg88gFyQp5ZXqq: {
        front: `What is Chakra UI's goal?`,
        back: `To design simple, composable components that cater to real-life UI design problems.`,
        tags: [`9swD16I7e9S7p8cj2rAM`],
        createdDate: `Sun May 29 2022 14:39:14 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Sun May 29 2022 14:39:14 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      NTMpCht95eal9gdZuhyQ: {
        front: `Style Props`,
        back: `All component styles can be overridden or extended via style props to reduce the use of css prop or styled(). Compose new components from Box.`,
        tags: [`9swD16I7e9S7p8cj2rAM`],
        createdDate: `Sun May 29 2022 15:08:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Sun May 29 2022 15:08:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      NpBvvQfmrYqyQSj4P8Jj: {
        front: `Why does CSS not hide overflow by default?`,
        back: `Does not want to cause data loss. If there is data loss, then it may go unnoticed. For example, if the submit button on a form is overflow and is not shown then the user will not be able to submit the form and is really confused! But if the button is just overflowed onto another element then it's maybe not so bad.\n\nAlso, CSS trusts that the dev knows what they are doing and assumes you are managing the potential for overflow.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      NyRC5e81gERRZjV8AFGt: {
        front: `What type of environment do you prefer?`,
        back: `Collaborative, passionate and driven. Always seeking to improve.`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      O2a16yQodDXPb6OeuYQN: {
        front: `What should you do if the initialState for a useState hook is expensive to calculate?`,
        back: `You may provide a function as the initial state, which will be executed only on the initial render.\n\nconst [state, setState] = useState(() => {\n  // some expensive calculations\n  // make sure to return the initial state\n})`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      O6nLHZq03gaIiNRYgmiW: {
        front: `What's the alternative CSS box model?`,
        back: `Any \`width\` or \`height\` set will be the visible width and height instead of just the content's width and height. Useful for setting the "real" size of a box rather than having to add it up with the border and padding properties.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      OAuqM10ernyQLuzHbzEY: {
        front: `Are objects inside a deeply reactive object also proxies?`,
        back: `Yes`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      OOtEOgPKpb0u66ZP3i2e: {
        front: `Why did React historically throw an error when a component returned undefined? And why does React 18 now allow returning undefined?`,
        back: `Historically, the intent of this behavior was to help users catch a common issue of forgetting a return statement accidentally.\n\nHowever, at runtime you can't tell the difference between forgetting to return and explicitly returning undefined. But, this is something linting can check for. Linting has become robust enough that it can tell you when you are forgetting to return anything. So React now does not throw an error.`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ORKj3vMY7hHxwp85QlsQ: {
        front: `Universal Selectors`,
        back: `Matches elements of any type\n\n* {\n  color: green;\n}`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Oc1coAALtWccqdU4iFjj: {
        front: `The ___ method removes the first element from an array and returns that removed element.`,
        back: `// shift()\nconst arr = [1, 2, 3];\narr.shift(); // returns 1\n// arr is now [2, 3]`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Od3Y1LmcWzp8iW3DFi6b: {
        front: `When passing a function to a ref attribute, what happens?`,
        back: `The function will be called on each component update. Gives you full flexibility on where to store the element reference.\n\n<input :ref="(el) => { /* do whatever */ }">`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      OizbC1Wy5b6P1aQO8r2J: {
        front: `Explain the Lifecycle Diagram`,
        back: `1. Renderer encounters component\n2. setup (Composition API)\n3. Init Options API\n4. Has pre-compiled template?\n  i. No -> Compile template on the fly\n  ii. Yes -> Nothing\n5. initial render create & insert DOM nodes\n6. Is now mounted\n7. When data changes\n  i. re-render and patch\n8. When component is unmounted, unmount`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      OpGq4Gmy2AilPtikbUv8: {
        front: `Why can defineProps and defineEmits not reference local variables declared in setup scope?`,
        back: `Because the options passed too defineProps and defineEmits will be hoisted out of setup into module scope.\n\nHowever, it can reference imported bindings.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      OrLQBzTQTMSVNt9G1Rin: {
        front: `Explain the useEffect hook and its syntax.`,
        back: `useEffect(() => {\n  // a side effect that should happen\n}, [dep, anotherDep]);\n\nAfter each render, the effectful callback will be run. If the dependency array is passed in, the callback will only run if one of the dependencies changed.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      OwGvGbEqdOlLAdtNn6Bd: {
        front: `The ___ method returns a new Array iterator object that contains the keys for each index in the array.`,
        back: `// keys()\n\nconst arr = ['foo', 'bar', 'baz'];\nconst iterator = arr.keys();\n\nfor (const key of iterator) {\n  console.log(key);\n}\n\n// 0\n// 1\n// 2`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      P1VjsuSnwSxRy27H3J5D: {
        front: `What is Declarative Rendering?`,
        back: `Vue extends standard HTML within a template syntax that allows us to declaratively describe HTML output based on JavaScript state.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      P1qrYCABgtWc8WmDQbjp: {
        front: `What's the goal for Suspense?`,
        back: `The goal is to extend support for Suspense so that eventually, the same declarative Suspense fallback can handle any asynchronous operation (loading code, data, images, etc.).`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      P4nhKmlBhcClOziyWv9p: {
        front: `What's the shorthand for the v-on directive?`,
        back: `@\n\n<button v-on:click="doThis"></button>\n<button @click="doThis"></button>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      PMrutcyaf6UIWvLlQhAE: {
        front: `Why did you leave Kroger?`,
        back: `I learned a lot at Kroger. I worked there for several years, but decided that the environment was not the right fit for me. I'm really looking for an environment where everyone is constantly driven to improving things.`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      PZwdg7GHGP4X8uOvoge1: {
        front: `What does Suspense do?`,
        back: `Lets you declaratively specify the loading state for a part of the component tree if it's not yet ready to be displayed.`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      PaT1d6fOauyaGVUL0gtN: {
        front: `How do you turn on the alternative box model for an element?`,
        back: `box-sizing: border-box`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      PcyqR4AemFntQmmRR85f: {
        front: `parseInt('hello', 10);`,
        back: `NaN`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      PfrtUGThqObfTEmFeMl1: {
        front: `What is an internal stylesheet?`,
        back: `An internal stylesheet resides within an HTMl document by placing CSS inside a <style> element inside the HTML <head>\n\n<head>\n  <style>\n    p { color: green; }\n  </style>\n</head>`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      PkZ9CjWaehQhiboR7G3z: {
        front: `typeof 32`,
        back: `number`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      QEn644vaOF1nOAQRZUTo: {
        front: `How does React know the difference between built-in components (like div) and user defined components?`,
        back: `Whether the first letter is capitalized.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 17:05:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 17:05:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      QMeUqqtyhC9b3BaAMl4v: {
        front: `What's the value of a declared variable that was not assigned a value?`,
        back: `undefined`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      QPpl77RJAXC9WHQAINm4: {
        front: `The ___ method removes the last element from an array and returns that element.`,
        back: `const arr = [1, 2, 3];\narr.pop(); // 3\n// arr is now [1, 2];`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      QdmlqU4NSFuH0HQkUVaN: {
        front: `Under the hood, what does Vue do?`,
        back: `Vue compiles the templates into highly-optimized JavaScript code.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      QeOZCrvGt8GaYIEcu6Cc: {
        front: `Pseudo Elements`,
        back: `A keyword added to a selector that lets you style a specific part of the selected element.\n\nselector::pseudo-element { }`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      QkBk0cULIiskeamMnpmD: {
        front: `Are all Vue templates syntactically valid HTML that can be parsed by spec-compliant browsers and HTML parsers?`,
        back: `Yes.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      R1dm8XiKaRt6R8YJdJwD: {
        front: `Greatest Strength`,
        back: `Customer obsession. It's important to me that the customer is getting a good experience, and if I think there's a bad experience then i think it should be fixed.`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      R3tPlGcLPZGVRuvXIoyr: {
        front: `Number.isNan(undefined);`,
        back: `false`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      RaIVmUdjAmUA2irlfs8E: {
        front: `How do you enable the new concurrent renderer?`,
        back: `By switching to use createRoot instead of ReactDOM.render`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      RbHHPYPnhJ37r5vnCS7i: {
        front: `What does \`display: flex\` do?`,
        back: `Sets the outer display type to \`block\` and changes the inner display type to \`flex\`. Any direct children will become flex items.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      RnYBVBRV6uR5qPfKZMB1: {
        front: `What is overflow?`,
        back: `When there is too much content to fit in a container.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      RuE2n2A9hNU5AMEKZi75: {
        front: `When was the first edition published?`,
        back: `1997`,
        tags: [`pM9S35qYvsjLjcmWQPZQ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      S0Eo8iAz9uTtcl4Npf6Q: {
        front: `let x = 3;\ny = ++x;\n\nWhat is x and y?`,
        back: `// x = 4\n// y = 4`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      S3PkvcUQLLgAr45l6IN3: {
        front: `What types can reactive() work for?`,
        back: `Object types (objects, arrays and collection types). Cannot hold primitives.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      S3TZOvJlKq3lff0N1Ysv: {
        front: `ad hoc`,
        back: `When necessary or needed.`,
        tags: [`Xf92QQ7BHRe67htkGzcP`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      S47Vmz0uVWY3PC5A5hg9: {
        front: `How can you do inline styles?`,
        back: `<div :style="{color: activeColor }"></div>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      SI7a0zh9Z9eiA93xYDFD: {
        front: `How do async functions work?`,
        back: `Basically I say "Hey, run this code. And after you run it, run this other code based off the results." Typically the code inside a promise will be non-blocking, such as an http request. This allows other synchronous code to run.`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      SRsT6NAjBeLwKeigEA4V: {
        front: `What happens when you access an element in an array with a negative index?`,
        back: `Returns undefined.\n\nconst arr = [1, 2, 3];\narr[-1]; // undefined`,
        tags: [`iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`, `JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      SXVLqruVrfiPRtRJhFs5: {
        front: `What's special about observed array's mutation methods?`,
        back: `Vue wraps them so they will also trigger view updates.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Sp2DPRBhKZN3uxWBouxx: {
        front: `What is Selective Hydration?`,
        back: `When using the <Suspense> component, React can hydrate other components before hydrating the component within <Suspense>.\n\nBasically, you're selecting to hydrate part of your app first before doing the rest.\n\nIn addition, when multiple components wrapped in Suspense React will smartly prioritize the most urgent part of the screen based on user interaction.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      SyA1x9wDGVfcId9NNbeh: {
        front: `What's the naming convention for composable functions?`,
        back: `camelCase names that state with "use"`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 07 2022 15:51:10 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 07 2022 15:51:10 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      SyLYsK3l4KtLHo8Wsja6: {
        front: `What properties on a reactive object are not unwrapped when accessed?`,
        back: `A reactive array or native collection like Map.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      T0EgfeOuA1C9xrvNEcYK: {
        front: `What does Next.js provide?`,
        back: `A React framework that basically handles all the building and tooling for you.`,
        tags: [`Rfe3j22KJ7nh5UjVB2y4`],
        createdDate: `Fri Jun 17 2022 13:59:12 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Fri Jun 17 2022 13:59:12 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      T5wPvQW0RvcxQXkkqggZ: {
        front: `What is an external stylesheet?`,
        back: `An external stylesheet contains CSS in a separate file with a \`.css\` extension.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      T66dKm2anci0OyBnsnCV: {
        front: `When should you use the useLayoutEffect hook?`,
        back: `If you need to mutate the DOM and/or need to perform measurements.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      TAl9GyGE4ATOGEzIzkpD: {
        front: `Do you need to unwrap a ref in templates?`,
        back: `No. When refs are accessed as top-level properties in the template they are automatically unwrapped so there is no need to use .value.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      TRwfYZnGqgKLuZxqZoHK: {
        front: `Explain toRefs()`,
        back: `Converts a reactive object to a plain object where each property of the resulting object is a ref pointing to the corresponding property of the original object. Each individual ref is created using \`toRef()\`.\n\nconst state = reactive({ foo: 1, bar: 2 });\nconst stateAsRefs = toRefs(state);\n/*\n  Type of stateAsRefs: {\n    foo: Ref<number;\n    bar: Ref<number;\n  }\n*/\n\nstate.foo++;\n// stateAsRefs.foo.value is now 2\n\nstateAsRefs.foo.value++;\n// state.foo is now 3`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      TYou8w9t5R6mue1xZYaa: {
        front: `Ecma International`,
        back: `An organization that creates standards for technologies.`,
        tags: [`VEiy15IEyjnO0RbmH8FV`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      TddhkXbxsyVetcmjLoC2: {
        front: `In the future, React would like to add a feature that allows React to add and remove sections of the UI while preserving state. For example, when a user tabs away from a screen and back, React should be able to immediately show the previous the screen.\n\nTo help surface these issues, React 18 introduces a new development-only check to Strict Mode. Explain this.`,
        back: `Before the change, React would mount the component and create the effects.\n\nWith Strict Mode in React 18, React will simulate unmounting and remounting the component in development mode.`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      TjhDZz2lCi9Ec4rcEOt5: {
        front: `Explain the v-else-if directive`,
        back: `Denotes the "else if block" for v-if. Can be chained.\n\nPrevious sibling element must have v-if or v-else-if\n\n<div v-if="something"></div>\n<div v-else-if="another"></div>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      TxMJLfk1WwCzLlVbX6Xl: {
        front: `Explain the useContext hook and the syntax.`,
        back: `const value = useContext(MyContext);\n\nAccepts a context object (the value returned from React.createContext) and returns the current context value for that context.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      TyGvI6tWM7Pu47os7Jev: {
        front: `Explain the steps of SSR.`,
        back: `• On the server, fetch data for the entire app.\n• Then, on the server, render the entire app to HTML and send it in the response.\n• Then, on the client, load the JavaScript code for the entire app.\n• Then, on the client, connect the JavaScript logic to the server-generated HTML for the entire app (this is "hydration")`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      U6gAWjSEkoyj89olwxHc: {
        front: `What is a key property of Concurrent React?`,
        back: `That rendering is interruptible.\n\nBefore adding any concurrent features, updates are rendered in a single uninterrupted, synchronous transaction. In a concurrent render, React may start rendering an update, pause in the middle, then continue later. It may even abandon an in-progress render altogether.`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      UQECg0RLrMSie344Z063: {
        front: `What are the differences when handling events with React elements vs DOM elements?`,
        back: `- React events are named using camelCase, rather than lowercase.\n- With JSX you pass a function as the event handler, rather than a string.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Thu Jun 16 2022 14:45:20 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Thu Jun 16 2022 14:45:20 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      UWkGAL041w9mr0KbvHum: {
        front: `What's the difference between ES6 and ES2015?`,
        back: `They are the same thing. In 2015, Ecma decided to switch to annual releases and to name the new editions based on the year. So ECMAScript changed its name from ES6 to ES2015.`,
        tags: [`VEiy15IEyjnO0RbmH8FV`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      VHoM9S689zNl7uGDiGsz: {
        front: `How do you deal with pressure or stressful situations?`,
        back: `I realize stressful situations are going to occur. I like to be confident and ensure my focus is on the problem and how to solve it. Being practical and planning things out are important (time permitted).`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      VLX43tRwJq5fKfqS7IlS: {
        front: `Is state shallow or deeply reactive by default?`,
        back: `By default, state is deeply reactive. But there is a \`shallowReactive()\` function that is only reactive for root-level properties.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      VQHhqrUBidU6kEkYVwBn: {
        front: `What's the makings of a block box?`,
        back: `Margin, border, padding, content`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      VfgUBe5yEsbYhemZSPvY: {
        front: `What is a CSS ruleset? (or CSS rules?)`,
        back: `The paring of CSS declaration blocks with selectors.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Vx7YYLsy4RNoIxcCLGK3: {
        front: `ECMA-262`,
        back: `A standard published by Ecma International. It contains the specification for a general purpose scripting language.`,
        tags: [`VEiy15IEyjnO0RbmH8FV`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      WHWKU1LUPiVFwwPodbyj: {
        front: `Attribute Selector to force case sensitivity`,
        back: `[atter operator value s]\n\nAdding an s or S (only supported by Firefox)`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      WLXqAEcvabLwXJ3S1HWl: {
        front: `The ___ method creates a new array populated with the results of calling a provided function on every element in the calling array.`,
        back: `const arr = [1, 2, 3];\narr.map(x => x + 1); // [2, 3, 4]`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      WMAMBtfWj7fHj4ayIAFM: {
        front: `Example code of defineProps and defineEmits without TypeScript`,
        back: `<script setup>\nconst props = defineProps({\n  foo: String,\n  bar: String\n})\n\nconst emit = defineEmits(['change', 'delete'])\n\n</script>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      WSbKBEiE2TrccpVDhuZz: {
        front: `What does babel compile the following JSX to?\n\nconst element = (\n  <h1 className="greeting">\n    Hello, world!\n  </h1>\n);\n`,
        back: `const element = React.createElement(\n  'h1',\n  {className: 'greeting'},\n  'Hello, world!'\n);`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 16:13:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 16:13:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      WkszdWXnPqAJ9xQLuct1: {
        front: `What methods do react-dom/client provide?`,
        back: `createRoot and hydrateRoot`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      WlrEjCnIPhWFu2qOLirR: {
        front: `Attribute Selector whose value contains at least one occurence of \`value\` within the string`,
        back: `[attr*=value]`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      WqpVnSiRSEtde9czM981: {
        front: `What does hydrateRoot do?`,
        back: `Same as createRoot, but is used to hydrate a container whose HTML contents were rendered by ReactDOMServer. React will attempt to attach event listeners to the existing markup.\n\nhydrateRoot(container);`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      X4TgogsCNe4E79vOBfuD: {
        front: `How can overflow be hidden?`,
        back: `overflow: hidden;`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      XBOS0SDUECXUxki4RayZ: {
        front: `What's the problem that React Testing Library tries to solve?`,
        back: `Maintainable, avoid implementation details, focus on confidence, and changes to implementation but not functionality do not break tests.\n\nYou want to write maintainable tests for your React components. As a part of this goal, you want your tests to avoid including implementation details of your components and rather focus on making your tests give you the confidence for which they are intended. As part of this, you want your testbase to be maintainable in the long run so refactors of your components (changes to implementation but not functionality) don't break your tests and slow you and your team down.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `dAwfSnqSbKz6Vca6ybOr`],
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 01 2022 10:27:15 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 01 2022 10:27:15 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      XW0ceoyPz8kkWJ9dZ9qn: {
        front: `What is returned from reactive()?`,
        back: `A Proxy of the original object, which is not equal to the original object.\n\nconst raw = {};\nconst proxy = reactive(raw);\nproxy === raw; // false`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Xd6uSkSavC63uBMVTatY: {
        front: `Explain the useDebugValue hook and the syntax.`,
        back: `useDebugValue(value)\n\nuseDebugValue can be used to display a label for custom hooks in React DevTools.\n\n// More in depth example\nfunction useFriendStatus(friendID) {\n  const [isOnline, setIsOnline] = useState(null);\n\n  // ...\n\n  // Show a label in DevTools next to this Hook\n  // e.g. "FriendStatus: Online"\n  useDebugValue(isOnline ? 'Online' : 'Offline');\n\n  return isOnline;\n}`,
        tags: [`bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      XohUvv2M8JBb4AiM0wY0: {
        front: `What are the set of principles to help achieve Chakra UI's goal?`,
        back: `Style Props, Simplicity, Composition, Accessibility, Dark Mode, and Naming Props`,
        tags: [`9swD16I7e9S7p8cj2rAM`],
        createdDate: `Sun May 29 2022 15:07:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Sun May 29 2022 15:07:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Xr7smoDPd1yWZa0ia35B: {
        front: `Explain \`reactive()\``,
        back: `Returns a reactive proxy of the object.\n\nconst obj = reactive({ count: 0 });`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      XwX02B0PNFzGMNAsRT9a: {
        front: `What are the two different API styles of Vue?`,
        back: `Options API and Composition API`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Y0iBJt6WrUbK9r7MUPJD: {
        front: `What is "inheritance" in CSS?`,
        back: `Some CSS properties when set on an element are also given to all of the element's descendants.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      YGOZZa6ILIP697Leoxho: {
        front: `How can you put a JavaScript expression inside JSX?`,
        back: `Wrapping the expression in curly braces.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 15:58:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 15:58:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      YJ8R1RsuHn0n3CgCjNS8: {
        front: `How does a box with an outer display type of \`inline\` behave?`,
        back: `• The box will not break onto a new line\n• The \`width\` and \`height\` properties will not apply\n• Vertical padding, margins and borders will apply but will not cause other inline boxes to move away from the box\n• Horizontal padding, margins and borders will apply and will cause other inline boxes to move away from the box`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      YVgLiQhU9hV6XuP5ddWc: {
        front: `Define Concurrency`,
        back: `The ability to execute more than one program or task simultaneously.`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      YhEVB9rHOq2nqT2iL8FA: {
        front: `What does createRoot do?`,
        back: `Create a React root for the supplied container and return the root. The root can be used to render a React element into the DOM with render.\n\n// get your DOM element\nconst container = document.getElementById('root');\n// create a React root\nconst root = createRoot(container);\n// initial render\nroot.render(element);`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      YhY0J9F5ZgAFdP2hnB5r: {
        front: `When using SSR, can the user interact with the website after the HTML has been rendered on the client but before the JavaScript has been loaded and hydrated?`,
        back: `No. The page cannot be interactive before the JavaScript code for it fully loads.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      YwrPyowER19QAyxtRKmi: {
        front: `Can you have the plain class attribute with the :class directive?`,
        back: `Yes.\n\n<div class="static" :class="{ active: true }"></div>\nwill render\n<div class="static active"></div>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Z1ZaRGGe0EZfKH1iOvu2: {
        front: `How can you change multiple elements in an array to a new value?`,
        back: `// Mutates the array!!\nconst arr1 = [1, 2, 3];\narr1.fill('foo'); // ['foo', 'foo', 'foo']\nconst arr2 = [1, 2, 3];\narr2.fill('foo', 1); // [1, 'foo', 'foo']\nconst arr3 = [1, 2, 3];\narr3.fill('foo', 0, 2) // ['foo', 'foo', 3]`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ZC8c7xjxfxeAkgMDwfBv: {
        front: `What is the required preamble for an html document?`,
        back: `<!DOCTYPE html>`,
        tags: [`ISZSggUEy6bPvg4jlNjd`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ZDZvPDiScJcM7iTMync7: {
        front: `What is an IIFE?`,
        back: `A JavaScript function that runs as soon as it is defined.\n\n(function () {\n  ...\n})();`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ZG9wLD14ngPFUW7dsVZT: {
        front: `test 1`,
        back: `test 1`,
        tags: [`1926ww60kMmODntxvstd`],
        isDeleted: true,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 13 2022 17:30:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 13 2022 21:51:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ZK8h43r4Fjs3JNZ9Fnp8: {
        front: `What are some of the benefits of the Composition API?`,
        back: `• Better logic reuse\n• More flexible code organization\n• Better type inference\n• Smaller production bundle and less overhead (better minification)`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ZejTxZju2VIHMVu7cL6S: {
        front: `How to convert value to a boolean?`,
        back: `Boolean(value);\n!!(value);`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ZilSyDEdGAn8kRubosOg: {
        front: `Explain REST API`,
        back: `service requests and stuff`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ZvMqKGTwtyy3ozloBYnw: {
        front: `Explain \`margin: 0px 1px 2px 3px\``,
        back: `0px = top\n1px = right\n2px = bottom\n3px = left\n`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ZvtQ5fdWmbPeMSNVsh0b: {
        front: `When using SSR and Suspense, can the page be hydrated before the HTML has been streamed for a Suspense component?`,
        back: `Yes.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      aGFnrcSbhgF4YIvqp1y2: {
        front: `How can you create a new array with all sub-array element concatenated into it?`,
        back: `const arr = [0, 1, 2, [3, 4]];\narr.flat(); // [0, 1, 2, 3, 4]\nconst arr2 = [0, [[[1, 2]]]];\narr2.flat(2); // [0, [1, 2]]`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ahOtw7wgCVvXt9MbysxO: {
        front: `What is important to me? What am I looking for in an employer?`,
        back: `An environment of developers that are passionate and driven about the work they do. I want to be around other developers that inspire me.`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      amAS1R27TqlNDw0TGJtR: {
        front: `What are some of the major enhancements of ES2015?`,
        back: `Modules, class declarations, lexical block scoping, iterators and generators, promises for asynchronous programming, destructuring patterns, and proper tails calls.`,
        tags: [`pM9S35qYvsjLjcmWQPZQ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      aoC7R7ILT3czQqC1yGni: {
        front: `Why is PascalCase recommended for SFCs?`,
        back: `To differentiate from native HTML elements.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      bBIsE26aKnYYa6tE3r6j: {
        front: `What is a CSS selector?`,
        back: `A pattern of elements and other terms that tell the browser which HTML elements should be selected to have the CSS property values inside the rule applied to them.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      bHBpwmWUJkcrBjgBqL6O: {
        front: `A JavaScript engine`,
        back: `A program or interpreter that understands and executes JavaScript code.`,
        tags: [`VEiy15IEyjnO0RbmH8FV`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      bJrNhVFWmoDQ8J84hJf8: {
        front: `General Sibling Combinator`,
        back: `Matches all iterations of the second element, that are following the first element (not necessarily immediately) and are children of the same parent element.\n\nformer_element ~ target_element { style properties }`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      bMkX6tVxjMn7cDPM85Aw: {
        front: `Explain the v-cloak directive`,
        back: `Used to hide un-compiled template until it is ready. Only needed in no-build-step setups.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      bYoUYjREtieiTuCSak4F: {
        front: `Did this work?`,
        back: `I hope so!`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      bcipk3QeFI4rthU62LE6: {
        front: `What happens if a v-bind value is null or undefined?`,
        back: `The attribute will be removed from the rendered element.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      bvXTxXqF1bT8igxsoyon: {
        front: `What are CSS @rules?`,
        back: `Instructions for what CSS should perform or how it should behave. An example is @media for media queries.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      bzbJV3yCrJQR3bYDMkwv: {
        front: `What is the old and new method to create a root render?`,
        back: `New: createRoot\nOld: ReactDOM.render`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      bzsO1FZ3lsObTIilI9qY: {
        front: `How can you shorten an array?`,
        back: `const arr = [1, 2, 3];\narr.length = 2; // arr is now [1, 2]`,
        tags: [`iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`, `JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      c6xrj5Mk9worakU5jq2a: {
        front: `ECMAScript 6`,
        back: `The sixth edition of the ECMA-262 standard, and features major changes and improvements to the ECMAScript specification.`,
        tags: [`VEiy15IEyjnO0RbmH8FV`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      c7VYbHyVCun7IqtECsv6: {
        front: `How is <button @click="say('hello')">blah</button> handled?`,
        back: `This is treated as a JavaScript statement being passed in, so it's an inline handler instead of a method handler. Basically the result of \`say('hello')\` is not what is passed to @click, but rather the statement \`say('hello')\` is what is executed when the button is clicked on.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      cBJUbcDpc0KFa9leAyF3: {
        front: `How can you cleanup any side effects in \`watchEffect\`?`,
        back: `watchEffect((onCleanup) => {\n  // the () => whatever function will be called right before the next time the effect is re-run\n  onCleanup(() => whatever);\n}`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      cKYQEIb3YdAVmIMraSCY: {
        front: `Attribute Selector matches exact value`,
        back: `[attr=value]`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ca5u1TfScGvX8p1rt2xR: {
        front: `Explain the v-model directive`,
        back: `Creates a two-way binding on a form input element or a component.\n\nLimited to\n• <input>\n• <select>\n• <textarea>\n• components`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      caUpHYAYS50ODvsnnW6n: {
        front: `How can you get an Array Iterator object that contains key/value pairs for each index in an array?`,
        back: `const arr = ['foo', 'bar', 'baz'];\nconst iterator = arr.entries();\niterator.next().value; // [0, 'foo']\niterator.next().value; // [1, 'bar'];`,
        tags: [`iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`, `JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      cup71reOkhcAYB393ENe: {
        front: `Explain isProxy()`,
        back: `Checks if an object is a proxy created by reactive(), readonly(), shallowReactive() or shallowReadonly()`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      cvxoITdED8intcJG1Hik: {
        front: `When using composable, how should you handle inputs that could be a ref?`,
        back: `You can use \`unref(maybeRef)\` to get the value.\n\nIf your composable creates reactive effects when the input is a ref, make sure to either explicitly watch the ref with watch(), or call unref() inside a watchEffect() so that it is properly tracked.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 07 2022 15:56:12 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 07 2022 15:56:12 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      cxUUmYCAgQyy8LjDTqOz: {
        front: `Greatest Weakness`,
        back: `One of my areas of growth would be bias for action. Historically there have been times where I've taken longer on projects than I should've because of my desire to find a way to make something better. While I think it's important to improve stuff, I know there needs to be a balance between thinking of how to make stuff better and just making it better right now.`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      d93WAKPBdtuPEcrj0lep: {
        front: `What does renderToPipeableStream do? And where is it typically used?`,
        back: `New render function for SSR in React 18.\n\nRender a React element to its initial HTML. Returns a stream with a \`pipe(res)\` method to pipe the output and \`abort()\` to abort the request. Fully supports Suspense and streaming of HTML.\n\nTypically used on a Node server. And is only available in environments with Node.js streams.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      dIJCKG95yobF3vv71OXP: {
        front: `What happens when you pass a class attribute to a component with multiple root elements?`,
        back: `You would need to define which element will receive the class.\n\n// my-component\n<p :class="$attrs.class"></p>\n<span></span>\n\n// another file\n<my-component class="foo"></my-component>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      dUJJgxy0E7uUDCOFuFKf: {
        front: `What's the most difficult thing I have ever coded?`,
        back: `Idk`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      dWLZRlsOqsKZb7OXYL1r: {
        front: `Explain the v-text directive`,
        back: `Updates the element's text content.\n\n<span v-text="msg"></span>\n<!-- same as -->\n<span>{{ msg }}</span>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      daIIHBPMZiwWC2Ax7ZPk: {
        front: `What does <!DOCTYPE html> do?`,
        back: `It prevents the browser from switching into a “quirks mode” when rendering a document. There’s really no reason to ever use a different mode. In the beginning days of the web, browsers would use this to allow browsers to treat new standards compliant sites differently from old legacy sites.`,
        tags: [`ISZSggUEy6bPvg4jlNjd`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      dgsZE7Py3YEphKD4om3i: {
        front: `How does a method handler receives the native DOM event object that triggers it?`,
        back: `As an argument.\n\nfunction foo(event) {\n// stuff\n}\n<button @click="foo">bar</button>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      dja6nt89eFNy4nPDwKm4: {
        front: `What are inline styles?`,
        back: `CSS declarations that affect a single HTML element, contained within a \`style\` attribute. Avoid this as much as possible.\n\n<p style="color: green; background-color: black;">Hello there</p>`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      dpsuEVhlUaq40sF97fkz: {
        front: `How can you check if 2 arrays share a common element?`,
        back: `const found = arr1.some((value) => arr2.includes(value))`,
        tags: [`lB4kjB6sFIRBff8RfS1G`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      dwKr8jattU0yxlH8KHba: {
        front: `Explain the useSyncExternalStore hook and the syntax.`,
        back: `const state = useSyncExternalStore(subscribe, getSnapshot[, getServerSnapshot]);\n\nProvided for library authors to integrate libraries deeply into the React model, and are not typically used in application code.\n\nuseSyncExternalStore is a hook recommended for reading and subscribing from external data sources in a way that’s compatible with concurrent rendering features like selective hydration and time slicing.\n\nProbs will never need this, but maybe learn about it.`,
        tags: [`bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      e0ZrC6bKXMT7HwqYC9b8: {
        front: `The ___ method adds one or more elements to the end of an array and returns the new length of the array.`,
        back: `const arr = [1, 2, 3];\narr.push('foo'); // returns new length 4\n// arr is now [1, 2, 3, 'foo']`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      eFZ5u5PVt6O83kn11U0N: {
        front: `How do you use a ref with a v-for?`,
        back: `Make the ref an array, which will be populated with the elements after mount.\n\n// script setup\nconst itemRefs = ref([]);\n\n// template\n<div v-for item in items" ref=\nitemRefs"></div>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      eIBjL2u7DSNunxADWmRp: {
        front: `Define normative`,
        back: `Establishing, relating to, or deriving from a standard or norm, especially of behavior.`,
        tags: [`pM9S35qYvsjLjcmWQPZQ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      eMAOwd3np4vdh2LmyAXM: {
        front: `Explain the difference between different import/export implementations and require and import`,
        back: `ES6: import export, synchronous and asynchronous\n\nCommonJS: require and exports, synchronous, server development,\n\nNodeJS: require and module.exports, synchronous, checks for node_modules\n\nAMD: asynchronous, designed for use in browsers, require and exports`,
        tags: [`iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 09:09:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 09:09:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      eUSiQ7J3neUixUQT0ylw: {
        front: `What are the arithmetic operators?`,
        back: `+ Addition\n- Subtraction\n/ Division\n* Multiplication\n% Remainder\n** Exponentiation`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      eWQd4sMYhpS9xsaDy5Q2: {
        front: `Can tuples have rest elements?`,
        back: `Yes. Tuples can have rest elements, which have to be an array/tuple type. A tuple with a rest element has no set length - it only has a set of well-known elements in different positions.\n\ntype StringNumberBooleans = [string, number, ...boolean[]];\ntype StringBooleansNumber = [string, ...boolean[], number];\ntype BooleansStringNumber = [...boolean[], string, number];`,
        tags: [`jcosukteLxJC3SKg6STx`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 13:11:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 13:11:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ebAYzDWzpvf3TonlEVGd: {
        front: `What is SSR?`,
        back: `Server-side rendering. Allows you to generate HTML from React components on the server, and send that HTML to your users.`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      enltFnO1see4fiwlg6yP: {
        front: `What is the prefix and postfix increment? And what is the difference between them?`,
        back: `Prefix is ++x\nPostfix is x++\n\n++x increments the value first, then returns the value\nx++ returns the value of x first, then increments the value\n`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      eoFBm3AOboRGRtBsJ1fN: {
        front: `Explain key when using v-for`,
        back: `When not using key, Vue uses an "in-place patch" strategy. If the order of the data items has changed, instead of moving the DOM elements to match the order of the items, Vue will patch each element in-place and make sure it reflects what should be rendered at that particular index. This is bad when your render output relies on child component state or temporary DOM state (e.g. form value).\n\nTo allow Vue to properly track each node's identity, provide a unique key attribute for each item.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      epOCF1tYlderu2RgDpSc: {
        front: `Tell me about a time you had to push back to HQ or challenged a decision.`,
        back: `Maybe Integration team errors?`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      erlhIovbOWfYEk8qONHT: {
        front: `For defineProps and defineEmits, can you use complex types and type imports from other files?`,
        back: `No, it is currently not possible and will result in a run-time error when the component is trying to render.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      f3sZ0eQIdYbRK5DXpLAi: {
        front: `The ___ method returns a string representing the specified array and its elements.`,
        back: `const arr = [1, 2, 3, 'a']\narr.toString(); // '1,2,3,a'`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      f6Q0pMIwGjlfjQtumLns: {
        front: `Can you pass an array to :class?`,
        back: `Yes. The below is allowed.\n\n<div :class="[{ active: isActive }, errorClass]"></div>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      fc1IMXkhwYcFpVdPSLuP: {
        front: `When using a ref on a child component, what's the difference between Options API and Composition API?`,
        back: `If the child is using Options API, the ref will be identical to the child's \`this\`, which means the parent will have full access to every property and method.\n\nIf the child is using Composition API, the ref will not have access to anything unless the child exposes a public interface using the \`defineExpose\` macro.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      flNyZx63IErvhwMlrNj7: {
        front: `What are strings?`,
        back: `Sequences of Unicode characters. They are sequences of UTF-16 code units; each code unit is represented by a 16-bit number.`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      fm8nt4reBlrazYPA3a9O: {
        front: `How can you dynamically switch between components?`,
        back: `Using the <component> element with the \`is\` attribute. \`is\` can contain either the name string of a registered component or the actual imported component object.\n\n<component :is="tabs[currentTab"></component>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      fqUj8qamW0OUQfYbvDUa: {
        front: `What does short-circuit logic on && and || mean?`,
        back: `Whether they will execute their second operand is dependent on the first.`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      fyNSJOAhXrpIqwlxzpQ0: {
        front: `What is the CSS box model?`,
        back: `The box model defines how the different parts of the box (margin, border, padding, content) work together to create a box that you can see on a page. It applies to block boxes, and only some of the behavior is applied to inline boxes.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      g6fFdM0d7gvu8QSFBhQY: {
        front: `Does @types/react and @types/react-dom require you to explicitly define children?`,
        back: `Yes. This is new in React 18.\n\ninterface MyProps {\n  children?: React.ReactNode;\n}`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      gLc6pnoGLAiQnvqIB2NP: {
        front: `What's the shorthand for v-bind?`,
        back: `<div v-bind:id="dynamicId"></div>\n\n<div :id="dynamicId"></div>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      gLx7T25NhI0PcWiRu8aK: {
        front: `Explain imperative vs functional`,
        back: `Seems like in functional, you don't really change a value of any variables. The variables are set, and that's their value. Also, pure functions.\n\nYou don't assign a variable a value, you declare that a variable is equal to some value.`,
        tags: [`KxYIVkAnI7lWJRbJMQvm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      gQ5wuqbE8fPxRnYUNYEM: {
        front: `Can you unmount a React root?`,
        back: `Yes.\n\nroot.unmount();`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      gSlCxWsJ2dCeXeJXsOXs: {
        front: `What are the 2 broad categories which you can test React components?`,
        back: `Rendering component trees in a simplified test environment and asserting on their output.\n\nRunning a complete app in a realistic browser environment (end-to-end tests)`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `dAwfSnqSbKz6Vca6ybOr`],
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 01 2022 10:10:18 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 01 2022 10:10:18 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      gWfgyjOWqPVme9PZrc3Z: {
        front: `What does \`watch\` allow us to do compared to \`watchEffect\`?`,
        back: `• Perform the side effect lazily\n• Be more specific about what state should trigger the watcher to re-run\n• Access both the previous and current value of the watched state`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      gfqYAhBZ7PeecvZhXUeI: {
        front: `What is the most complicated feature you have developed?`,
        back: `Maybe the monetization analytics`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ghu4r7WN9kZ5MOFVabkp: {
        front: `Can you recursively call a function?`,
        back: `Yes.\n\nfunction blah() {\n  if (something) {\n    blah();\n  }\n}`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      giPNGhhZ5D2l9H7Q0lNl: {
        front: `1 / 0;`,
        back: `Infinity`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      gnIvZuRIrotwS0vG1AWB: {
        front: `Code example of defineProps and defineEmits using TypeScript`,
        back: `<script setup lang="ts">\n\nconst props = defineProps<{\n  foo: string;\n  bar?: number;\n}>()\n\nconst emit = defineEmits<{\n  (e: 'change', id: number): void;\n  (e: 'update', value: string): void;\n}>()\n\n</script>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      gsuWkpvTIJlWpK1S0SjP: {
        front: `Attribute Selector`,
        back: `Matches elements based on the presence or value of a given attribute.\n\n/* <a> elements with a title attribute */\na[title] {\n  color: green;\n}`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      h7OAB8yqlpFnJtfpO2NK: {
        front: `What property defines an element's type of box?`,
        back: `The \`display\` property`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      hBp12Dn9ap3adzlhqUWm: {
        front: `Accessibility`,
        back: `When creating a component, keep accessibility top of mind. This includes keyboard navigation, focus management, color contrast, voice over, and the correct aria-* attributes.`,
        tags: [`9swD16I7e9S7p8cj2rAM`],
        createdDate: `Sun May 29 2022 15:10:12 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Sun May 29 2022 15:10:12 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      hFRmHZNiThlEnJFN7cUn: {
        front: `How long can JavaScript expressions can be used in a Vue template binding?`,
        back: `Only one.\n\n// bad, this is a statement not an expression\n{{ var a = 1 }}\n\n// bad, use ternary expression instead\n{{ if (ok) { return message } }}`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      hGGcnFFEP5Xj6YAzTaQe: {
        front: `How can you create a new, shallow-copied Array instance from an array-like or iterable object?`,
        back: `Array.from('foo'); // ['f', 'o', 'o']\nArray.from([1, 2, 3]); // new array of [1, 2, 3]\n\nCan also map over array as second argument.\nArray.from([1, 2, 3], x => x + 1); // [2, 3, 4]`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      hHZ0Ysn7PlgsvgVvQU7Y: {
        front: `Why should you always pass the radix to parseInt?`,
        back: `In the case it's not specified then it will be set automatically based on the value. For example, "010" will be detected as an octal number.\n\nAlso the method could be implemented differently in different versions of JavaScript and browsers.`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      hiIJdO2jHamImbeay4rm: {
        front: `Scripting Language`,
        back: `A programming language that is used to manipulate, customize, and automate the facilities of an existing system`,
        tags: [`pM9S35qYvsjLjcmWQPZQ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      hrkbFcFJGXwU6mUp3J1l: {
        front: `What are Transition updates?`,
        back: `Transition the UI from one view to another.`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      i3blrqpimr5Rg9IAffRL: {
        front: `What does tearing mean?`,
        back: `Tearing is a term traditionally used in graphics programming to refer to a visual inconsistency.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      iCZY9uQmVeerA7D3QGAf: {
        front: `How can you create a new array with all elements that pass some criteria?`,
        back: `const arr = [1, 2, 3];\narr.filter(x => x > 1); // [2, 3]`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ir4as8XMJuCBrRgYgz0e: {
        front: `Explain \`computed()\``,
        back: `Takes a getter function and returns a readonly reactive ref object for the returned value from the getter. It can also take an object with \`get\` and \`set\` functions to create a writable ref object.\n\nconst count = ref(1);\nconst plusOne = computed(() => count.value + 1);`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      jB3Bo0ogmuwGkhWjvoxd: {
        front: `What's the difference between a "reference of an object" and an "instance of an object"?`,
        back: `The actual object is an instance.\n\nThe variables used to access the object hold the references to the instance.`,
        tags: [`iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`, `KxYIVkAnI7lWJRbJMQvm`, `HPGpTmMLX4iFKog2u5Rm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      jHIpx5SOdGlOTFc4H9oS: {
        front: `How can you access the original DOM event in an inline handler?`,
        back: `<button @click="foo('bar', $event)"></button\n<button @click="(event) => foo('bar', event)"></button>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      jQ9sLRPUc4XDGE2B3tBv: {
        front: `When was the sixth edition adopted?`,
        back: `2015`,
        tags: [`pM9S35qYvsjLjcmWQPZQ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      jX9heP3tFD9N0KhoJFNp: {
        front: `Explain the v-else directive`,
        back: `Denotes an "else block" for v-if or a v-if / v-else-if chain.\n\nPrevious sibling element must have v-if or v-else if.\n\n<div v-if="something"></div>\n<div v-else></div>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      jyFtqYA8CGW3x6CHIvbc: {
        front: `Is JavaScript case-sensitive?`,
        back: `Yes.`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      k75lJV7p4ULqBp9CFt4o: {
        front: `What does CSS do?`,
        back: `Describes how elements should be stylized/rendered.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      k8uX4t7uqxKPaIsqGB2I: {
        front: `Does createRoot modify the container node?`,
        back: `No. Only modifies the children of the container.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      k9Qzpbmjrt0Tyau1hmOG: {
        front: `switch (1) {\n  case 1:\n    console.log("One");\n  default:\n    console.log("Default");\n}`,
        back: `One\nDefault`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      k9zixIJGD2GDjJbllmaX: {
        front: `Why should computed getters be side-effect free?`,
        back: `Its only responsibility should be computing and returning a value.`,
        tags: [],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      kMsqSvD04yI2SUoQcuwZ: {
        front: `Explain the v-memo directive`,
        back: `Introduced in Vue 3.2+\n\nMemoize a sub-tree of the template. If every value in the array was the same as last render, then updates for the entire sub-tree will be skipped.\n\n<div v-memo="[valueA, valueB">...</div>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      kPNF8bIxmSYM1X2WJ0kI: {
        front: `What's the difference between a computed property and a normal function?`,
        back: `Computed properties are cached based on their reactive dependencies. A normal function will always run the function whenever a re-render happens.`,
        tags: [],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      kXb37mVH6aZDhj2nvKRI: {
        front: `The ___ method returns the last index at which a given element can be found in the array, or -1 if it is not present. The array is searched backwards, starting at fromIndex.`,
        back: `// lastIndexOf()\nconst arr = ['foo', 'bar', 'foo'];\narr.lastIndexOf('foo'); // 2\narr.lastIndexOf('foo', 1); // 0`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      kj4RQMGvbkX9VcB34Oiq: {
        front: `Explain \`readonly()\``,
        back: `Takes an object (reactive or plain) or a ref and returns a readonly proxy to the original.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      kpVRIsGQOEx1M2GvTV8P: {
        front: `Why is hydration called hydration?`,
        back: `It's like watering the "dry" HTML with the "water" of interactivity and event handlers.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ky9ke0MHo75hl418P0LV: {
        front: `Dark Mode`,
        back: `Make components dark mode compatible. Use useColorMode hook to handle styling.`,
        tags: [`9swD16I7e9S7p8cj2rAM`],
        createdDate: `Sun May 29 2022 15:10:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Sun May 29 2022 15:10:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      kySEs66HyxbkU5PzUmyP: {
        front: `How can you bind a v-model's value to a dynamic property instead of the default value?`,
        back: `<input\n  type="checkbox"\n  v-model="toggle"\n  true-false="yup"\n  false-value="nope" />`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      lEag7MwNqTMR678SdCUf: {
        front: `What is JSX?`,
        back: `A syntax extension to JavaScript. Similar looking to XML.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 15:56:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 15:56:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      lYkTc7k8tdQrQbkMVe8E: {
        front: `if (new Boolean(false)) {\n  // will this if statement's body be executed?\n}`,
        back: `Yes`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      loRiOGsGuz5ZmptDEV7A: {
        front: `What's the syntax for adding a CSS file to an HTML page?`,
        back: `You should put it within head (but it will still load outside of head)\n\n<head>\n  <link rel="stylesheet" href="styles.css">\n</head>`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      lpIei1oMCjWHAQLLQBZI: {
        front: `test 5.2`,
        back: `test 5.2`,
        tags: [`1926ww60kMmODntxvstd`],
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 13 2022 21:51:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 13 2022 21:52:07 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      lpqPZ9aB2ov0WzjVLnJz: {
        front: `Explain the v-once directive`,
        back: `Render the element and component once only, and skip future updates.\n\n<span v-once>This will never change: {{ msg }}</span>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      maNQNlA94ZJZ7gV6GyZH: {
        front: `ECMA-402`,
        back: `Provides key language sensitive functionality as a complement to ECMA-262.`,
        tags: [`VEiy15IEyjnO0RbmH8FV`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      mhOl6OHE5O5jFiqDn5ug: {
        front: `What is the increment operator and what does it do?`,
        back: `++\n\nAdds one to its operand and returns a value.`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      mqzJIrOp5uqpTNEDyeCw: {
        front: `Explain the v-pre directive`,
        back: `Skip compilation for this element and all its children. Most common use case is displaying raw mustache tags.\n\n<span v-pre>{{ this will not be compiled }}</span>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      mv8QzR5qtdWqAKgn9Sod: {
        front: `How can you get the index of an element in an array?`,
        back: `const arr = ['foo', 'bar', 'baz'];\narr.indexOf('bar'); // 1\narr.indexOf('blah'); // -1`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      mwBtCcSt0puDyRI8ZnhI: {
        front: `Column Combinator`,
        back: `Experimental, no browser support.\n\nMatches only those elements matched by the second selector belong to the column elements matched by the first.\n\ncolumn-selector || cell-selector { style properties }`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      mzEBOpPZxoPwtvH3k7kO: {
        front: `Explain the useImperativeHandle hook and the syntax.`,
        back: `useImperativeHandle(ref, createHandle, [deps])\n\nuseImperativeHandle customizes the instance value that is exposed to parent components when using ref. As always, imperative code using refs should be avoided in most cases. useImperativeHandle should be used with forwardRef.\n\nBasically, there's this forwardRef function that allows the parent component to pass a ref to a child component. That child component can then do something with that ref, for example attach it to a DOM node, and the parent will then have access to that DOM node that is within the child component. Using the useImperativeHandle hook, instead of attaching the ref to a DOM node the child component can pass the ref to the useImperativeHandle hook and customize the instance value of it, for example create some functions that the parent can then access.`,
        tags: [`bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      n1ftgELDUe5a26CPEGPP: {
        front: `How can you create an object?`,
        back: `const obj1 = { a: 'foo', b: 'bar' }; // Preferred\nconst obj2 = new Object({a: 'foo', b: 'bar'});\nconst obj3 = Object.create({a: 'foo', b: 'bar'});`,
        tags: [`HPGpTmMLX4iFKog2u5Rm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      n7rOi7nnJJOcOcu6KP2N: {
        front: `What is a fundamental aspect of the web?`,
        back: `Links.`,
        tags: [`ISZSggUEy6bPvg4jlNjd`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      nBI4reRbbw3XcaD6WdJh: {
        front: `Does React support Internet Explorer?`,
        back: `As of React 18, React no longer supports Internet Explorer.`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      nNV0excQLFKwnyOtI2rf: {
        front: `How can you create a new application instance?`,
        back: `import { createApp } from 'vue';\n\nconst app = createApp({\n  /* root component options */\n});\napp.mount('#app'); // can be either a DOM element or a selector string`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      nQdRrFjrKJdvRFNsGzC0: {
        front: `switch (1) {\n  case 1:\n    console.log("One");\n  case 2:\n    console.log("Two");\n}`,
        back: `One\nTwo`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      nc1pIsz8qSdJafKPxu0c: {
        front: `What happens when calling reactive() on the same object?`,
        back: `Always returns the same proxy.\n\nconst raw = {};\nconst proxy = reactive(raw);\nreactive(raw) === proxy; // true\nreactive(proxy) === proxy; // true`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      neFZwaSM3vIqvkhZebl1: {
        front: `How can you check whether a value is an Array?`,
        back: `Array.isArray([1, 2, 3]); // true\nArray.isArray('foo'); // false`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      nhTJOp6SozGddRsQoiCZ: {
        front: `Edit this `,
        back: `back`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      nuV9Fgg95gqKn3nAK5aY: {
        front: `What's a good example for an Urgent update and a Transition update?`,
        back: `When you select a filter in a dropdown, you expect the filter button itself to respond immediately when you click. However, the actual results may transition separately. Also, if you change the filter again before the results are done rendering, you only care to see the latest results.`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      nzUPtgoHWF23anbvjgrB: {
        front: `Do computed properties automatically track its reactive dependencies?`,
        back: `Yes, so computed properties will update any bindings that depend on itself when a reactive dependency changes.`,
        tags: [],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      nzjFDGQSfuMQ5RWpKodM: {
        front: `What 2 technologies is ECMAScript based on?`,
        back: `JavaScript and JScript`,
        tags: [`pM9S35qYvsjLjcmWQPZQ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      o3w4uHnVjQPn9XtjoEtb: {
        front: `Can you access globals in binding template expressions?`,
        back: `Yes, but you are limited to a restricted list.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      oAIjtOZz5LkAuAEm8zrw: {
        front: `What do you mean by functional testing?`,
        back: `Testing functionality on a page with automation and on real web browsers. Examples include adding items to cart, adding payment methods to account, checking out.`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      oAqrFQnFM1BtJuNaqwZu: {
        front: `Attribute Selector whose exact value is in a whitespace-separated list of words`,
        back: `[attr~=value]`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      oHMhckr7eQboMIwAyhg7: {
        front: `test 2`,
        back: `test 2`,
        tags: [`1926ww60kMmODntxvstd`],
        isDeleted: true,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 13 2022 17:30:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 13 2022 17:31:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      oKF84EuTolikBzC7Dtth: {
        front: `Attribute Selector without case sensitivty`,
        back: `[attr operator value i]\n\nAdding an i or I before the closing bracket. (no IE support)`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      oTh05gjvVvMXcdlGsgg8: {
        front: `What is a necessary consequence of concurrency?`,
        back: `If you want to be able to interrupt rendering to respond to user input for more responsive experiences, you need to be resilient to the data you're rendering changing and causing the user interface to tear.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ohLvU1v4bcC6Cl9Yr4i7: {
        front: `Why is it safe to embed user input in JSX?`,
        back: `By default, React DOM escapes any values embedded in JSX before rendering them. And everything is converted to a string before being rendered`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 16:12:05 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 16:12:05 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ohZMhUo5kMVjwiyuEcP3: {
        front: `Explain unref()`,
        back: `Returns the inner value if the argument is a ref, otherwise return the argument itself. This is a sugar function for \`foo = isRef(val) ? val.value : val\`\n\nconst value = unref(x);`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      owTjsdhFmZxzR7b2BYhM: {
        front: `What happens when using v-for and v-if together?`,
        back: `v-if has a higher priority, so v-if will not have access to variables from the scope of the v-for\n\n// throws an error because "item" is not defined\n<div v--for="item in stuff" v-if="item"></div>\n\nInstead, use a template\n\n<template v-for="item in stuff">\n  <div v-if="item"></div>\n</template>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      p8vJk0EFxT50BqqrPMxR: {
        front: `Heyyyyyyyyyyyyasdf`,
        back: `Ohhhhhhhhhhhh`,
        tags: [`UQFZObstxz4gOWDWaxKo`, `ktYuM92Bbqu35Rj6jENC`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 10:29:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Fri May 27 2022 11:20:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      pQwAOMUKA9fdLQmcoSTi: {
        front: `What happens if you don't add a break statement to a switch case?`,
        back: `The execution will "fall through" to the next level.`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      pUZ3tOq6ASdtNxR9nQ7J: {
        front: `The ___ method returns a shallow copy of a portion of an array into a new array object selected from \`start\` to \`end\`.`,
        back: `const arr = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5];\narr.slice(1); // [2, 3, 4, 5]\narr.slice(1, 3); // [2, 3]\narr.slice(-2); // [4, 5];\narr.slice(2, -1); // [3, 4]`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      pfaxc5oWqyHpgRCGSzkW: {
        front: `What are the main parts of an HTML element?`,
        back: `The opening tag, closing tag, content, and attributes.`,
        tags: [`ISZSggUEy6bPvg4jlNjd`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      pg5xM3RiH8COIhFqCcMf: {
        front: `Hope this has a date!`,
        back: `Woohoooooooooooo`,
        tags: [`ktYuM92Bbqu35Rj6jENC`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      plqTnDSRzncOTyVDS5R7: {
        front: `How can you defer formatting useDebugValue values?`,
        back: `useDebugValue accepts a function as a second parameter that is only called if the hooks are inspected. It receives the debug value as a parameter and should return a formatted display value.\n\nuseDebugValue(date, date => date.toDateString());`,
        tags: [`bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      pmNeGAno5dOwKYREyrdy: {
        front: `Explain the v-on directive`,
        back: `Attach an event listener to the element\n\n<button v-on:click="doThis"></button>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      prakubo1KNjjAiowSntx: {
        front: `What is memoization?`,
        back: `In computing, memoization is an optimization technique used primarily to speed up computer programs by storing the results of expensive function calls and returning the cached result when the same inputs occur again.`,
        tags: [`KxYIVkAnI7lWJRbJMQvm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      psjf7v53HTUMBTGTjqrK: {
        front: `When using composables, what is the recommended convention for a return value of multiple values?`,
        back: `Always return an object of refs from composables so that it can be destructured while retaining reactivity.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 07 2022 15:58:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 07 2022 15:58:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      pxyKVv75XvxkI0On6WwC: {
        front: `What are Server Components?`,
        back: `Upcoming feature that allows developers to build apps that span the server and client, combining the rich interactivity of client-side apps with the improved performance of traditional server rendering.`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      q58a82qGGSphrWPBYnRV: {
        front: `How can you convert a string to a number?`,
        back: `Number('123'); // 123\nNumber('0xF'); // 15\n\nparseInt('123', 10); // 123\nparseInt('0xF', 16); // 15\n\nparseFloat('123'); // 123\n\n+ '42'; // 42\n+ "0x10"; // 16\n`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      qEbAi1KHErbAtnLDmFYu: {
        front: `Explain \`watch()\``,
        back: `Watches one or more reactive data sources and invokes a callback function when the sources change.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      qdTZrxxCNFV9RMLpHs0e: {
        front: `What is a composable?`,
        back: `A composable is a function that leverages Vue Composition API to encapsulate and reuse stateful logic.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 07 2022 15:42:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 07 2022 15:42:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      qlxdMTCKz3VwIBlEs8zn: {
        front: `Attribute Selector whose value is suffixed by \`value\``,
        back: `[attr$=value]`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      qn2ZskMXRMh95NQaSRFS: {
        front: `The ___ method returns a new Array Iterator object that contains the values for each index in the array.`,
        back: `const arr = ['foo', 'bar', 'baz'];\nconst iterator = arr.values();\nfor (const x of iterator) {\n  console.log(x);\n}\n// foo\n// bar\n// baz`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      qsUlEwDWYPMYIvNGfAYA: {
        front: `The ___ method changes the contents of an array by removing or replacing existing elements and/or adding new elements.`,
        back: `// splice()\nconst arr1 = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5];\narr1.splice(1); // returns [2, 3, 4, 5]\n// arr1 is now [1]\n\nconst arr2 = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5];\narr2.splice(2, 2); // returns [3, 4]\n// arr2 is now [1, 2, 5]\n\nconst arr3 = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5];\narr3.splice(2, 2, 'foo', 'bar', 'baz'); // returns [3, 4]\n// arr3 is now [1, 2, 'foo', 'bar', 'baz', 5]`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      qyNTZ8EJdwk83jOS6IL8: {
        front: `isNaN(undefined);`,
        back: `true`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      rKxadevjQfHhWU6i3XDX: {
        front: `The ___ method adds one or more elements to the beginning of an array and returns the new length of the array.`,
        back: `// unshift()\nconst arr = [1, 2, 3];\narr.unshift(4)\n// arr = [4, 1, 2, 3];\narr.unshift(5, 6);\n// arr = [5, 6, 4, 1, 2, 3]`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      rLBM85qpIS8EmFsmuZz0: {
        front: `What is a shorthand property?`,
        back: `A property that allows the setting of multiple properties in a single line.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      rZhZFL20ruJtIhdBcfq2: {
        front: `Non-null assertion operator?`,
        back: `The non-null assertion operator may be used to assert that its operand is non-null and non-undefined in contexts where the type checker is unable to conclude that fact.\n\nBasically, it excludes null and undefined from the type.\n\nTo use it, simply post-fix your variable with !\n\n// Compiled with --strictNullChecks\nfunction validateEntity(e?: Entity) {\n  // Throw exception if e is null or invalid entity\n}\n\nfunction processEntity(e?: Entity) {\n  validateEntity(e);\n  let s = e!.name; // Assert that e is non-null and access name\n}`,
        tags: [`jcosukteLxJC3SKg6STx`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      rdcJ1YUPhXvBpIDCA1u6: {
        front: `Can defineProps and defineEmits use both runtime declaration and type declaration?`,
        back: `No. Using both at the same time will result in a compile error.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      rkmtmNc1yyYwYJlARWcZ: {
        front: `How can you infer an array literal as a tuple?`,
        back: `let a = [3, 4] as const;\nlet b = <const>[3, 4];\n\nNote that this sets it as a readonly tuple.`,
        tags: [`jcosukteLxJC3SKg6STx`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 13:13:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 13:13:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      rkzrs1O6TWN9O6jDpYou: {
        front: `ID Selector`,
        back: `Matches an element based on the value of an elements \`id\` attribute.\n\n#foo {\n  color: green;\n}`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      rl6ZnbWeFoA9wu4RTGhp: {
        front: `How can you get the index of an element in an array that satisfies some condition?`,
        back: `const arr = [1, 2, 3];\narr.findIndex(x => x > 1); // 1 (the index where 2 is)\narr.findIndex(x => x > 4); // -1`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      rlF6NVdks3AyX3iWLhI6: {
        front: `What is the Options API?`,
        back: `With Options API, we define a component's logic using an object of options such as \`data\`, \`methods\` and \`mounted\`. Properties defined by options are exposed on \`this\` inside functions, which points to the component instance.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ry3fCKPMnNYwVrpFF3E2: {
        front: `Class Selector`,
        back: `Matches elements based on the contents of their \`class\` attribute\n\n.some_class {\n  color: green;\n}`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      s7vwKTPmRF178jk4L8d1: {
        front: `What is similar to instance variables in a React component?`,
        back: `The useRef hook. The ref object is a generic container whose current property is mutable and can hold any value, similar to an instance property on a class.`,
        tags: [`bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      sFgR8eZLTHwJUniE5WdP: {
        front: `How can you create a string from elements in an array?`,
        back: `const arr = ['foo', 'bar', 'baz'];\narr.join(); // 'foo,bar,baz'\narr.join(''); // 'foobarbaz'\narr.join('-'); // 'foo-bar-baz'`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      sGuZBEwJ34A84KnV18Ic: {
        front: `What is React hydration?`,
        back: `The process of rendering your components and attaching event handlers is known as "hydration".\n\nReact hydration is a technique used that is similar to rendering, but instead of having an empty DOM to render all of our react components into, we have a DOM that has already been built, with all our components rendered as HTML.`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      sQ85Tddct5g49rFiSu3E: {
        front: `What is an inline handler?`,
        back: `Inline JavaScript to be executed when an event is triggered.\n\n<button @click="count++">Add 1</button>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      sQxbhYdrDa5lCIcScHcB: {
        front: `Define text interpolation`,
        back: `interpolation: the insertion of something of a different nature into something else\n\nIn Vue, the most basic form of data binding is text interpolation using the "Mustache" syntax (double curly braces)\n\n<span>Message: {{ msg }}</span>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      sUfF1eW2bFt8DryPLu34: {
        front: `What does createRoot do with any existing DOM elements inside its container?`,
        back: `Any existing DOM elements inside are replaced when render is called.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      sVrkYE2r0MWb4PAApwhT: {
        front: `Pseudo Classes`,
        back: `A keyword added to a selector that specifies a special state of the selected element. Many different pseudo-class available for elements.\n\nselector:pseudo-class { }`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      sfWxQEEmVBDKcALiLsXW: {
        front: `What does renderToReadableStream do?`,
        back: `Streams a React element to its initial HTML. Returns a Promise that resolves to a Readable Stream.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      shRkM395w8t6t3mEuIym: {
        front: `Explain the v-if directive`,
        back: `Conditionally render an element or a template fragment based on the truthy-ness of the expression value.\n\nWhen toggled, the element and its contained directives/components are destroyed and re-constructed.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      sjHLGWMkYzM8BkdacOEt: {
        front: `Explain toRef()`,
        back: `Can be used to create a ref for a property on a source reactive object. The created ref is synced with its source property: mutating the source property will update the ref, and vice-versa.\n\nconst state = reactive({ foo: 1, bar: 2 });\nconst fooRef = toRef(state, 'foo');\n\nfooRef.value++;\n// state.foo is now 2\nstate.foo++;\n// fooRef.value is now 3`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      t2nwmmnrhXHVIaf4DCX2: {
        front: `What's the difference between ES6 and ES2015?`,
        back: `They are the same thing.`,
        tags: [`pM9S35qYvsjLjcmWQPZQ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      tEVwM6GmpSjXx1cUjluc: {
        front: `Explain a modifier`,
        back: `Modifiers are special postfixes denoted by a dot, which indicate that a directive should be bound in some special way.\n\n<form @submit.prevent="onSubmit">...</form>\n`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      tGzRnNkB82r4ULdqjJSB: {
        front: `Explain a setter`,
        back: `A setter can be used to execute a function whenever a specified property is attempted to be changed.\n\nMust have exactly one parameter.\n\nconst o = {\n  set x(y) {\n    this.z.push(y);\n  },\n  z: []\n}\no.x = 4; // o.z is now [4]\no.x = 5; // o.z is now [4, 5]`,
        tags: [`HPGpTmMLX4iFKog2u5Rm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      tKXoNkyVmS1EWHUbaawk: {
        front: `-1 / 0;`,
        back: `-Infinity`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      tNmwfxT5tfjeOJcec5Ox: {
        front: `What are props?`,
        back: `Custom attributes you can register on a component.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      tZsgj8vp9sh794uMfnau: {
        front: `The ___ method sorts the elements of an array and returns the sorted array.`,
        back: `const arr = [2, 1, 4];\narr.sort();\n// Mutates, so arr is now [1, 2, 4]`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      teQpq8CSvDA5V9chKs1m: {
        front: `Babel`,
        back: `A transpiler that can convert ES6 code to ES5 code.`,
        tags: [`VEiy15IEyjnO0RbmH8FV`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ti42YLS6wX10vF7VBApt: {
        front: `Tell me about a time you stepped into a leadership role.`,
        back: `Volunteering for Integration team.\n`,
        tags: [`DOyCRHozacsc96HX2tFm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      tkAVSNqo4N23uA7fCsA2: {
        front: `Explain the useId hook and the syntax.`,
        back: `const id = useId();\n\nUsed for generating unique IDs that are stable across the server and client, while avoiding hydration mismatches.\n\nI don't know much about SSR, so learn more about this.`,
        tags: [`bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      tqV9ty0Q59tobpjUzDMf: {
        front: `What's the Padding box?`,
        back: `The padding sits around the content box as white space. Can be controlled using \`padding\` and related properties.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      tslHljMmkzn83p7OK5wm: {
        front: `How can you use non-mutating methods on an array to update the array?`,
        back: `Replace the old array with the new one. Vue implements some smart stuff to allow this.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      tsmtXqWPTZGKMl0DLC1B: {
        front: `How can you create an array?`,
        back: `const arr1 = ['Foo', 'Bar']; // Basically, always use the literal syntax\n\nconst arr2 = new Array(2); // length of 2 with undefined elements\nconst arr3 = new Array('Foo', 'Bar');\n\nconst arr4 = Array.of(2); // [2]`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      tuDZy5Nwrqbg3GW0UZpR: {
        front: `How can you assign a getter on an existing object?`,
        back: `const o = { a: 0 };\nObject.defineProperty(o, 'b', { get: function() { return this.a + 1 } });`,
        tags: [`HPGpTmMLX4iFKog2u5Rm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      twvgXi2F7G8tCLeHs288: {
        front: `What is a Koa application?`,
        back: `A Koa application is an object containing an array of middleware functions which are composed and executed in a stack-like manner upon request.`,
        tags: [`e1lSpuuIdmovubAEkSMR`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      u93w24GDVqgsqX6QGa7u: {
        front: `Adjacent Sibling Combinator`,
        back: `Matches the second element only if it immediately follows the first element and both are children of the same parent element.\n\nformer_element + target_element { style properties }`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      uLolwSsRh89igOyz28rU: {
        front: `What are the two types of boxes in CSS?`,
        back: `Block boxes and inline boxes`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      uNfoy47WfkfryegLyywq: {
        front: `What is a directive?`,
        back: `Directives are attributes prefixed with \`v-\` to indicate that they are special attributes provided by Vue. They apply special reactive behavior to the rendered DOM.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      uVnuHLcoqQ6UejRRkikL: {
        front: `Explain the useTransition hook and the syntax.`,
        back: `const [isPending, startTransition] = useTransition();\n\nReturns a stateful value for the pending state of the transition, and a function to start it.\n\nBasically, seems like it's a way to kinda defer state updates that aren't super important or may lead to an undesired UI. Need to read more about React 18 to fully understand this.`,
        tags: [`bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      vqWNR7evDG1F9RXdym5y: {
        front: `How do you get the number of elements in an array?`,
        back: `const arr1 = [1, 2, 3];\narr1.length; // 3`,
        tags: [`iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`, `JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      vsbIGrw7RXD9R8JN8aVf: {
        front: `Boolean(null);`,
        back: `false`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      w7AgXLGzefAPxdIv9Ent: {
        front: `How can you control inheritance in CSS?`,
        back: `CSS provides special universal property values to control inheritance. These properties are\n\ninherit, initial, revert, revert-layer and unset`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      wQ67rQMw7G5slSYC2JmK: {
        front: `Will most components just work when upgrading to React 18?`,
        back: `Yes.`,
        tags: [`yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      wSHUGAnSvk340svSCswU: {
        front: `What's the relationship between a component and an element?`,
        back: `A component given props will return an element.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 16:58:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 16:58:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      wVLaiyaTxT7aoT0lBEKv: {
        front: `By default, <component> unmounts components when switching. How can you force the inactive components to stay alive?`,
        back: `<KeepAlive>\n  <component is="foo" />\n</KeeppAlive>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      wYPLTfePUOXk1kR85d48: {
        front: `Does useRef notify you when it's content changes?`,
        back: `No. Mutating the .current property doesn't cause a re-render.`,
        tags: [`bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      wZTCqmIC8QdltGJ9KjUu: {
        front: `Why does React DOM use camelCase property naming convention for HTML attribute?`,
        back: `Because JSX is closer to JavaScript than to HTML.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 16:10:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 16:10:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      wesJkhuMwGueZiMFWJK4: {
        front: `A scripting language`,
        back: `A programming language designed specifically for acting on an existing entity or system.`,
        tags: [`VEiy15IEyjnO0RbmH8FV`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      wfhRIxGuy40YeVQWZC31: {
        front: `What's the difference between useEffect and useLayoutEffect?`,
        back: `useEffect fires after layout and paint, during a deferred event.\nuseLayoutEffect fires synchronously after all DOM mutations.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      wfj9NomjDv7KpVntq42Y: {
        front: `reduceRight vs reduce`,
        back: `reduceRight is same as reduce, but goes from right to left`,
        tags: [`JcT73dHQEFLfHiXnDiIy`, `iizxW3dBB55HDapBS5M6`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      wk0hYzj3TWQtpIityN9o: {
        front: `tuple type`,
        back: `A tuple type is another sort of Array type that knows exactly how many elements it contains, and exactly which types it contains at specific positions.\n\ntype StringNumberPair = [string, number];`,
        tags: [`jcosukteLxJC3SKg6STx`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 13:08:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 13:08:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      wmX3eDhft1rztxTyHCUN: {
        front: `What's an example of Options API in code?`,
        back: `<script>\nexport default {\n  data() {\n    return { count: 0 }\n  },\n  methods: {\n    increment() { this.count++ }\n  },\n  mounted() {\n    console.log(\`The initial count is \${this.count}.\`)\n  }\n</script>\n\n<template>\n  <button @click="increment">Count is: {{ count }}</button>\n</template>`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      wqDrxc7PQKglr68rNQ1P: {
        front: `What values coerce to false?`,
        back: `false, 0, empty strings (""), NaN, null, and undefined`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      wtymRgkrOuDHdYRK31Lt: {
        front: `How can you obtain a direct reference to a specific DOM element or child component instance after it's mounted?`,
        back: `The \`ref\` attribute using a reactive ref.\n\n// script setup\nconst input = ref(null)\n\n// template\n<input ref="input">`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ww1ORt7ZBebapDKVgvzH: {
        front: `Explain react-dom/client`,
        back: `The react-dom/client package provides client-specific methods used for initializing an app on the client.\n\n`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      x2JDJHZl5o4Mv8ufDpuZ: {
        front: `Why is SSR useful?`,
        back: `It allows users with worse connections start reading content while the JavaScript is loading.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      x5hCuaK0L2fumiFvqsOk: {
        front: `Explain the useDeferredValue hook and the syntax.`,
        back: `const deferredValue = useDeferredValue(value);\n\nFancy new React stuff in React 18 that I don't know anything about yet. From what I've read so far though, React 18 introduces non-urgent renders that can basically allow you to start new effects without and React can choose whether to throw away the render or not (or maybe you choose what conditions cause it to throw away).`,
        tags: [`bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      xCduZEDrk92aVQD2eWG7: {
        front: `parseInt("42a", 10);`,
        back: `42`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      xHqWvKo4LJbWcd9o6fbw: {
        front: `What does "cascading" mean in CSS?`,
        back: `Stylesheets cascade, meaning the order of the CSS matters. When 2 rules apply that have equal specificity, the one that comes last in the CSS is the one that will be used.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      xRZwDTNbLnpOFwR1nccY: {
        front: `Explain the useMemo hook and the syntax.`,
        back: `const memoizedValue = useMemo(() => computeExpensiveValue(a, b), [a, b]);\n\nReturns a memoized value that will only recompute when one of the dependencies change.`,
        tags: [`bzBBL7X267nhxV4cLtbm`, `mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      xm7HrOFnkzRPG1r2sIbq: {
        front: `Boolean(false);`,
        back: `false`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      xsJ8a9sbXMnrfWQxuMsE: {
        front: `By default, are user-created watcher callbacks called before or after Vue component updates?`,
        back: `Before. This means if you attempt to access the DOM inside a watcher callback, the DOM will be in the state before Vue has applied any updates.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      xtxoBDZMCNadvl5FLFMz: {
        front: `Can a Number have decimals?`,
        back: `Yes.\n\nconsole.log(3 / 2); // 1.5`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      yA2Cbdrs7MBDxodLwUWu: {
        front: `ECMAScript`,
        back: `The specification defined in ECMA-262 for creating a general purpose scripting language.`,
        tags: [`VEiy15IEyjnO0RbmH8FV`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      yBPvxr7IZKvMtm8n9vjJ: {
        front: `isNaN({});`,
        back: `true`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      yG5yERwFv1vVeQIsWQTF: {
        front: `Child Combinator/Selector`,
        back: `It matches only those elements matched by the second selector that are the direct children of elements matched by the first.\n\nselector1 > selector2 { style properties }`,
        tags: [`r0uscGSg1yNsb562pScw`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      yGfO40Zvi9EvHEQsMQtK: {
        front: `JavaScript`,
        back: `A general purpose scripting language that conforms to the ECMAScript specification.`,
        tags: [`VEiy15IEyjnO0RbmH8FV`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      yKS4dVRGsi5yMujdn0eI: {
        front: `What are the two core features of Vue?`,
        back: `Declarative Rendering and Reactivity`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      yLdS1DcfBvnupqRmYkWz: {
        front: `How does React 18 solve for "You have to load everything before you can hydrate anything"?`,
        back: `The Suspense component. If you wrap a component with <Suspense>, React will let you hydrate rest of the app before that component's JavaScript.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `yJT00Ez2trxmCJ4WT9IL`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      yLnqOAaTxJKIC8okAJnS: {
        front: `What's the smallest React example look like?`,
        back: `const root = ReactDOM.createRoot(document.getElementById('root'));\nroot.render(<h1>Hello, world!</h1>);`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`],
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 13:41:15 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 13:41:15 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      yccE8jbbBa3Gu3bCSSQf: {
        front: `"hello" + " world";`,
        back: `// "hello world"`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      yldmvdpdO9EdKGumTqoj: {
        front: `What's the difference between null and undefined?`,
        back: `undefined means a variable has been declared but has not yet been assigned a value\n\nnull is an assignment value, which can be used as a representation of no value`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ypL5qxLQSj2lZMgK0kLM: {
        front: `What's the available syntax options for v-for?`,
        back: `Expects an array, object, number, string or iterable\n\n<div v-for="item in items"></div>\n<div v-for="(item, index) in items"></div>\n<div v-for="(value, key) in object"</div>\n<div v-for="(value, name, index) in object">/div>\n<div v-for="n in 10"></div> // will repeat 10 times, starts with 1`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      yuVBUjXf3BWD9VnjKd1f: {
        front: `What is React Testing Library's primary guiding principle?`,
        back: `The more your tests resemble the way your software is used, the more confidence they can give you.`,
        tags: [`mgBzwFgbcvDsw7unZ2dU`, `dAwfSnqSbKz6Vca6ybOr`],
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 01 2022 10:27:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 01 2022 10:27:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      z1AA8bgTqN0tssfjHQEZ: {
        front: `What does the \`setup\` attribute do?`,
        back: `The \`setup\` attribute is a hint that makes Vue perform compile-time transforms that allow us to use Composition API with less boilerplate. For example, imports and top-level variables/functions declared in \`<script setup>\` are directly usable in the template.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      z7CyCCTXXILXJDnLgg5X: {
        front: `What is !important?`,
        back: `Makes a particular property the most specific, overriding the normal rules of cascade.`,
        tags: [`QiTrHu5t5L3mHbAv9WkY`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      zUndj8iU1OixjyZI4Qwi: {
        front: `isFinite(1 / 0);`,
        back: `false`,
        tags: [`2bpfIG2C3uOUal2cJeod`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      zWHtpAOcNsdEYgXfv3V4: {
        front: `Why is Vue called the "Progressive Framework"?`,
        back: `Because it's a framework that can grow with you and adapt to your needs.`,
        tags: [`21U6MpbMyPIYF4hGAtlZ`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:24 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:24 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      zp63PieVV6M8oeeLGqTs: {
        front: `What happens with the following?\n\nconst a = { x: 1, x: 2};`,
        back: `a is { x: 2}`,
        tags: [`HPGpTmMLX4iFKog2u5Rm`],
        createdDate: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:24 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue May 24 2022 09:23:24 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      zz5955EJxjdQ5E4eAWlt: {
        front: `test 6`,
        back: `test 6`,
        tags: [`1926ww60kMmODntxvstd`],
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 13 2022 21:51:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 13 2022 21:51:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
    },
  },
  reviews: {
    reviews: {
      "0SiEZdoEd20PlDxRF3iU": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `F6twCJwYOxmA8RRcybW8`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:15:16 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:15:16 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "0hseTBz8TkmYbHGLGPrR": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `Xd6uSkSavC63uBMVTatY`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:07:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:07:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "0rVbqa3EKBZrhLV3nXJC": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `sVrkYE2r0MWb4PAApwhT`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:23:18 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:23:18 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "18w8O2rZRMX9S2ncEtwL": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `ACJaYPj3uH4SMM2S5Mt3`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:49:24 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:49:24 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "1DWTBeE08kF5rbUzCh4h": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `f6Q0pMIwGjlfjQtumLns`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:42:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:42:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "1IDkzBnRGdCrEJDFEA9g": {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `YJ8R1RsuHn0n3CgCjNS8`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:20:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:20:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "1LFhFNrFrutTv4OsqajL": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `u93w24GDVqgsqX6QGa7u`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:23:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:23:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "1S3xDN0XzOfMH1cB2R8G": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `MXH6Vhpwmgt4Qi2WXjeZ`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:13:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:13:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "1iAjW8EcrGWN3MWe7XbI": {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `mqzJIrOp5uqpTNEDyeCw`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:56:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:56:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "1uaxWTQeuxBHOByTcsuZ": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `EYpGtN7wXQ1hYNDOZd5b`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:53:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:53:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "25yaphCiIowsfupnEtuW": {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `BDwvYS2QP4FbnXV4H1lU`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:09:13 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:09:13 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "2WYN5JvkpkM6CX2FRgm2": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `FHA4nmG7JGYFflVbZf49`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:53:24 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:53:24 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "35tcZxaj7TLWZ26Cnfdc": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `yG5yERwFv1vVeQIsWQTF`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:23:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:23:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "3AO3NYoySm8DZnoJwj9u": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `VQHhqrUBidU6kEkYVwBn`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:16:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:16:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "4AIoeOvw4MEd4gZ2ZQeg": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `dWLZRlsOqsKZb7OXYL1r`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:37:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:37:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "4BFq1xIQVRnP4hB1kXwg": {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `amAS1R27TqlNDw0TGJtR`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:43:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:43:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "4D4g92bEqmSNe70nFxQR": {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `tslHljMmkzn83p7OK5wm`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:07:13 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:07:13 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "4Jw6nWdAyBqD3WgBvKgt": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `ohZMhUo5kMVjwiyuEcP3`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:00:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:00:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "4UvtMGbiBuehguDekfWD": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `ZK8h43r4Fjs3JNZ9Fnp8`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:32:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:32:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "4lLKih7TS6bwVIp99Ypg": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `rkzrs1O6TWN9O6jDpYou`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:23:10 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:23:10 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "4zXkpI5lKC3HLlGF5PWT": {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `uNfoy47WfkfryegLyywq`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:07:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:07:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "5J8mYDhn871GB6FZ02RJ": {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `879MJ6HSbAQ9UdLD7aNV`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:41:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:41:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "5QAXilA7fyllh0gcSKGi": {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `75pzujJeS73jeCC8M8H0`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:46:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:46:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "5SObbenOoSRHuAxnnNSx": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `TxMJLfk1WwCzLlVbX6Xl`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:02:10 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:02:10 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "5t2zBmXU63ZUzKm0zlqe": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `qEbAi1KHErbAtnLDmFYu`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:03:20 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:03:20 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "6GVO0uLWmD6FpXcQaEDE": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `INrR1awLPLBK8ZUZ0QoY`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:53:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:53:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "6ZHsSzCfgo2B0ouz53cG": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `PfrtUGThqObfTEmFeMl1`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:15:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:15:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "6ZU7w1mJV3a7Q2xhuskx": {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `Ayg3BcZmlFWkM1PxeCV4`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:51:07 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:51:07 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "75keGPowQcJWi4v8F14a": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `s7vwKTPmRF178jk4L8d1`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:56:13 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:56:13 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "7ICvRD9wgsXcCTf5pb7P": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `M6SPNBhPw1g5EnjXOEZT`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:57:12 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:57:12 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "7MKflxOKS8OOFgR1POsg": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `gQ5wuqbE8fPxRnYUNYEM`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:41:23 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:41:23 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "7eGvDrZD6UqEHauCefzW": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `bvXTxXqF1bT8igxsoyon`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:21:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:21:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "7i08iQNomHFRchhAkQJr": {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `oAqrFQnFM1BtJuNaqwZu`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:22:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:22:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "7rkCf68f3TPM4bfCTHPN": {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `yuVBUjXf3BWD9VnjKd1f`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 12:01:17 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 12:01:17 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "7v9Arutwf6DITKk5j9u5": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `ZvtQ5fdWmbPeMSNVsh0b`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:39:16 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:39:16 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "8Wav5xFMoZySNlP44ONu": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `wfhRIxGuy40YeVQWZC31`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:59:22 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:59:22 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "8nONgBV0LIKcdSNyW7su": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `DjymydcM0fAuQ6EgweJ7`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:52:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:52:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "95PxVmXqlLv2OYMaOZhx": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `dja6nt89eFNy4nPDwKm4`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:21:23 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:21:23 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "9Ut8HdXIw6JjPPyx5Snt": {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `EkfGRsowiFbXPPXGmjnV`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:53:17 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:53:17 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      "9vr6LKu08wdyp5FoVtn0": {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `Xr7smoDPd1yWZa0ia35B`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:29:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:29:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      AufRMXqPShJ5j15AeZXf: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `TddhkXbxsyVetcmjLoC2`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:01:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:01:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      BF8AXqwWAJFFjOrRVeQU: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `mzEBOpPZxoPwtvH3k7kO`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:44:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:44:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      BeTxvsnqfygbZeCdD1Ga: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `xHqWvKo4LJbWcd9o6fbw`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:23:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      BkczIGvVmEdxHviDurnw: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `FMYE5tAD71LjQ53wWEYH`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:18:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:18:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      D2mwSl0CI0td6AH3MVAq: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `Ha8eE5baNdrBP917ngzm`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:51:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:51:56 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      D8BeGHQ6HAqiGk1H3eqh: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `23qkSrdQ2U94Vtsve6ao`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:37:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:37:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Dj7F0Cjsak7XT2sDBT45: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `zWHtpAOcNsdEYgXfv3V4`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:10:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:10:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      DlYmsRyV9C6mx64Bi89X: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `ry3fCKPMnNYwVrpFF3E2`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:23:12 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:23:12 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      EGbJZ3C4iJsRG6EbnTV1: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `O2a16yQodDXPb6OeuYQN`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:56:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:56:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      EZKPs4lnkoan54mWpAtW: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `rLBM85qpIS8EmFsmuZz0`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:23:10 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:23:10 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      EgVWDE0WCgUMWU5aJXJV: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `FhaiQOGVCPQdFpyF55hP`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:17:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:17:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      En0aIy2KFwcfTXCW18fB: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `bcipk3QeFI4rthU62LE6`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:34:18 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:34:18 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ErVO4Xvt77k0sfUSRWzK: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `6lBjglJfS59AMuMVnstN`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:07:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:07:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      EzLdnwK2sRGi1lvK1oHQ: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `9x2M8YegocZpR3hPzAsY`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:49:16 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:49:16 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      FIruMCLUPVFbmCXjxBuI: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `dwKr8jattU0yxlH8KHba`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:40:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:40:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      FLjANtjoXaND2FffFS9c: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `TAl9GyGE4ATOGEzIzkpD`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:27:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:27:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Fv8DuhxZHbJUYTa01iIM: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `YVgLiQhU9hV6XuP5ddWc`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:08:18 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:08:18 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      FzdGAlNTLG679wnW66LQ: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `8xooqSQsyCU7zrmEu3dL`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:08:17 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:08:17 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      GGDi88UHYpgWsE0EgjOT: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `bMkX6tVxjMn7cDPM85Aw`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:33:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:33:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      GSVYOwW1cw3cAg6HK7Rs: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `7Ny1uzvfd7tiRQWCpzPh`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:46:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:46:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Gfz4zJGjVjxB2w7X3d3b: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `hrkbFcFJGXwU6mUp3J1l`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:42:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:42:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      HTE7iDh7AjBlfXGxXj4a: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `jQ9sLRPUc4XDGE2B3tBv`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:44:17 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:44:17 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      HXbUMGo5zqn2A1QNN4Xv: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `wtymRgkrOuDHdYRK31Lt`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:09:23 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:09:23 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Hm0DX4RuQcViKN3Ya6QP: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `6N27zIa9NSangBpjl8fl`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:46:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:46:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      HvDBbGssaYYW4fFQ9W6I: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `T5wPvQW0RvcxQXkkqggZ`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:16:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:16:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      HvYZAwUjxQ4Uki5dcfCi: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `d93WAKPBdtuPEcrj0lep`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:40:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:40:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      IF9eTsKvktLhwJgAfyun: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `c7VYbHyVCun7IqtECsv6`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:34:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:34:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Ij6xfElQPMIx6wHg1vWV: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `ZvMqKGTwtyy3ozloBYnw`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:20:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:20:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      JHnMQglEw4FFuNvo7ATE: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `sjHLGWMkYzM8BkdacOEt`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:06:22 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:06:22 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      JJ9L2OPEceYQb73KmZ4Y: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `cup71reOkhcAYB393ENe`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:35:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:35:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      JOGs26C9Cr9VfIEbd0Qb: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `AsAeOZNbt1QxLoMiIfoj`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:08:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:08:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      JVYyXwNLg3siiHKi5QCD: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `QkBk0cULIiskeamMnpmD`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:18:07 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:18:07 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      JW9Zo52pcnFqWFFJ1NnU: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `i3blrqpimr5Rg9IAffRL`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:42:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:42:44 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      JWFkel1miGyvOrEnmBh9: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `5TKYGbbhBGsd1YnbRl6B`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:46:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:46:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      JepkEZCHOeggpclXB0AN: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `fm8nt4reBlrazYPA3a9O`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:43:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:43:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      JkyWGgrbajEwaUaLGQSG: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `HArJ4JImN6Iqz9quxRlI`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:54:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:54:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      KGNQ9PhkqzPaiP7dQwjB: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `loRiOGsGuz5ZmptDEV7A`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:23:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:23:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      KIfXSRli15HALBvpd5oe: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `oTh05gjvVvMXcdlGsgg8`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:55:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:55:32 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      KcFqHoZMI5vM2BdnCjgB: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `SyLYsK3l4KtLHo8Wsja6`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:27:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:27:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      KcM9598yCQY6tfd9lUmc: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `WkszdWXnPqAJ9xQLuct1`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:04:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:04:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      KixI92Z5z9MLrL0HALAI: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `WlrEjCnIPhWFu2qOLirR`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:19:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:19:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      KyPJjiAyMGDShfaswayp: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `EQMJnmAA5prbjp0JpXL3`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:18:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:18:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      LDTutBEJLQuSNUINbQUe: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `RbHHPYPnhJ37r5vnCS7i`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:16:05 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:16:05 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      LOCVAi4hVDqIiVvTJV2p: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `KXG1eEYYRvBQmoDwmKML`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:54:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:54:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      LQHRcNq6cfnCBc42GFMJ: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `qlxdMTCKz3VwIBlEs8zn`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:23:07 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:23:07 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      LZCG6KusyjMRK6ENFNxh: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `GsFIPGMzJvi35kIeeUbK`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:53:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:53:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Ljfhzka4Oq4fLY5PHB2u: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `0KyHfJRSx2xQYFOeJ10D`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:44:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:44:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      M1APhiDRLjFbuj8W549Q: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `BDhunSIg2wXWT8PcMn8b`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:51:21 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:51:21 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      M3HksGuI24kf1u4RdkBK: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `SyA1x9wDGVfcId9NNbeh`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:25:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:25:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      MLF4ELHUB74DsCTGaI2e: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `VLX43tRwJq5fKfqS7IlS`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:28:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:28:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      MSSab6iSFNajnQ55L9wI: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `eoFBm3AOboRGRtBsJ1fN`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:39:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:39:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      N9cwLYXutBOe1aktGmY5: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `OrLQBzTQTMSVNt9G1Rin`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:57:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:57:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      NBJrRRvgjR2ZbZJNZpiw: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `plqTnDSRzncOTyVDS5R7`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:55:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:55:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      NCAOkK5jQaUvUziM5rFn: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `gsuWkpvTIJlWpK1S0SjP`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:20:11 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:20:11 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      NJn8w2XZ2wtos1nDjpf0: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `DosiD3Gt1xL37cJkTSmL`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:52:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:52:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      NeztRQ15qsE4GYnr7Fin: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `RaIVmUdjAmUA2irlfs8E`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:59:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:59:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      NmYI5kWW7k0iTZoFLx6O: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `2DDI4XV9Jd2j3nGSIWlh`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:45:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:45:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      O49tjwpeDLClPv13dMZ3: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `lpqPZ9aB2ov0WzjVLnJz`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:54:16 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:54:16 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ODf9xjNoBGDbnjSQxoi0: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `7fXzCClAwDxt8DjfapAF`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:47:05 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:47:05 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Om7iNy1oG0g1DOdKxVGU: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `xRZwDTNbLnpOFwR1nccY`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 12:00:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 12:00:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      OnInJecmoPtU9TvL6VTY: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `69Lj8FuXDXilFcxqHtvl`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:45:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:45:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      OqIQZ42SZ5XTnGH3QeIY: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `8xz1mQPWAFgEw5ATasoI`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:47:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:47:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Oz6SD5hOitzlNmhn7Tpz: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `erlhIovbOWfYEk8qONHT`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:42:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:42:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      P36HUIgwsRDsR2kBLqd8: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `uLolwSsRh89igOyz28rU`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:23:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:23:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      P3BelV2rFtXwDUgLMEqh: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `E5Zrxar7BENXC676nSez`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:12:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:12:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      PQEWR4p6f4etKjOahwU7: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `ww1ORt7ZBebapDKVgvzH`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:59:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:59:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      PeKZPnP8Y5Clf8iXDvEg: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `0qHQLWx95NlwY3tSzTa3`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 10:49:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 10:49:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Q7haUYSJ5aBqJ2QJ6I20: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `fyNSJOAhXrpIqwlxzpQ0`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:21:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:21:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      QJye1e6c5Vmh6MeukEWW: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `eFZ5u5PVt6O83kn11U0N`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:39:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:39:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      QKkh3L2zUENOhGgWixHF: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `uVnuHLcoqQ6UejRRkikL`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:58:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:58:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      QVt84MHx1Xka9c9aQjHV: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `AdRUHA2B52MVuZU3Xgkj`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:18:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:18:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      QXJRDwGwBx2lbxrCVbQr: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `sUfF1eW2bFt8DryPLu34`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:57:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:57:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      QpsHEKoHWkAmEmVf1V9m: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `BBkj355rixxP0YoWahJl`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:50:15 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:50:15 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      QrbuWWDZIeCc9yNXnewM: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `EtCRIY3mCdVLnJJ9gVEU`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:42:10 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:42:10 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      R7gXs6HHnwf8xbUy7Bhu: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `sQ85Tddct5g49rFiSu3E`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:04:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:04:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      R8VrNitstHyER33pv6e4: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `Ai09VIyfjVgJK1AvgzmG`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:50:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:50:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      RDPSd14hXtXXmbfdZUue: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `XBOS0SDUECXUxki4RayZ`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:06:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:06:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      RLNYbIfdJcObVnXKshvi: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `CcIgWA8HpCiLb0W3c3Jo`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:10:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:10:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      RWzvLvOrO04fv3Hn04Md: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `hFRmHZNiThlEnJFN7cUn`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:45:22 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:45:22 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      RkFnV6GhPen7mwURi7qC: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `bJrNhVFWmoDQ8J84hJf8`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:19:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:19:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      RoPb9j2nXRJuHBlK0Tc9: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `8ygr6cyvpk06u2XL2xZO`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:48:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:48:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      RqkpaoDKknLdJR1lHD9Z: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `PZwdg7GHGP4X8uOvoge1`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:58:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:58:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      SCoRItlWhy6YKqvhEk6X: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `9avxzwyW43oVG5aY0ooT`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:48:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:48:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      SGSiv9IAEJVRGdjyqg64: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `TjhDZz2lCi9Ec4rcEOt5`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:27:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:27:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      TD8hV4aLfF6qt8VZ2pQn: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `x5hCuaK0L2fumiFvqsOk`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 12:00:24 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 12:00:24 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      THXuSy8WBADPncPCzfDd: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `bzbJV3yCrJQR3bYDMkwv`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:39:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:39:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      TOHx6GLhgWaHPARXUn0p: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `h7OAB8yqlpFnJtfpO2NK`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:21:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:21:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      TZw04Bm8sACl9ETtzyVe: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `LAL62vpqogTERTlkdlhR`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:55:12 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:55:12 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      TfnZpZ9vKIBWDocT3uSb: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `6L62Ld26x3nHlFndyi5e`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:46:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:46:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      TqFv9OUjryfUv05GbRbs: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `Y0iBJt6WrUbK9r7MUPJD`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:17:21 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:17:21 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      U0Y7hX7CKYGfHXb4ldxd: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `2u4sCQHU5McuFXviwOnH`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:41:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:41:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      U8oJPi89fPBIus244g2q: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `2n3liFnrsxfI4Lv1ktC9`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:45:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:45:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      UGLwYQVpctYZiCPli28C: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `Cz6ejbRERcHEW77S9P09`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:51:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:51:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      UJYDblizaeYepmWwDShH: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `X4TgogsCNe4E79vOBfuD`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:17:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:17:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      UoU8WZ0teMkbprq7oEAo: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `AYCI3QvhVBBNtA8qapbV`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:18:23 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:18:23 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      VG2QwF4CQs1eGCJmGR3U: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `rlF6NVdks3AyX3iWLhI6`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:04:15 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:04:15 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      VjT5q9AjYUIpFix4uEU6: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `Fp3ow41P23Yx0HeIZKX9`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:53:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:53:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      WR74c9MrBXyfMQE4tqQ8: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `T66dKm2anci0OyBnsnCV`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:00:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:00:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      WneSAi2Y4ukWNtffmre3: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `w7AgXLGzefAPxdIv9Ent`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:23:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      WrAm1sJX5TylmlRFPwKy: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `IMNOmTg0r0JrS2wxvqq8`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:53:11 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:53:11 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      XCR0ga7Qios5BlsbUjW4: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `9liIUNT36eo0TFd74hpw`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:49:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:49:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      XLXoefoRKtZz7KNxelCq: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `Ahm7TeSIqI7ONpoXoVfM`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:50:05 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:50:05 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      XPbNXtsrr1jb74wJzc0D: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `MgDoBifHpmQe7imkhOjo`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:55:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:55:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      XUpshER3pzUATBRZy1Xz: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `76joC4iJ7boAJVLkKlSq`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:46:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:46:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      XgirGvO01noR3MTUtlHX: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `MNwTF6hX2F60ZFJx5emZ`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:58:21 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:58:21 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      XxW0mmARE441xzOgjPee: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `ORKj3vMY7hHxwp85QlsQ`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:19:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:19:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      YBYuGc9QHDyUke5t4wyM: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `JgqAhRzgCsIZxJkuoezx`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:54:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:54:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      YKJv2DWUBqYsSUbPbRkt: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `0OTqiEYBEgHfezxv0YSq`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:45:06 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:45:06 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      YUGIXPqdEZMgBKei8lVG: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `OpGq4Gmy2AilPtikbUv8`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:16:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:16:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      YUpHboSHEr0XkLjkHGiB: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `F7jI6bKhrxXxmiqK7w3W`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:42:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:42:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      YaOs7mL9qzh0SJ51jjYv: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `PaT1d6fOauyaGVUL0gtN`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:15:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:15:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Yt4mfV60i9CZYJW7VfTI: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `BTHKMpFiSdxCy8hPrNqM`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:10:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:10:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ZNwOrD3sj3LCuXNeD36r: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `yLdS1DcfBvnupqRmYkWz`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 12:01:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 12:01:01 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Zjfw20seRcK2m53gEBIn: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `RuE2n2A9hNU5AMEKZi75`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:42:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:42:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      Zt9tlLLZF3Nv5s8ldeyZ: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `U6gAWjSEkoyj89olwxHc`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:04:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:04:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      a5KBEyAo8KlUyC5BqXCu: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `g6fFdM0d7gvu8QSFBhQY`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:40:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:40:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      aLjJh3dp31HZEvb4BDJT: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `jX9heP3tFD9N0KhoJFNp`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:52:23 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:52:23 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      asZJkGiQPNBXG9UNSLmY: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `fc1IMXkhwYcFpVdPSLuP`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:43:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:43:03 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      bHSZ0rNFNCOSvW12uK3J: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `wQ67rQMw7G5slSYC2JmK`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:58:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:58:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      bID1R6DyY8Oi2uWKkWNj: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `nBI4reRbbw3XcaD6WdJh`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:44:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:44:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      bP2P9ofahQtt7sxABv8M: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `I1MwpyJh6yHPlKdpmmUe`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:54:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:54:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      bsTburlT6UZmv9DWLWEY: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `WqpVnSiRSEtde9czM981`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:05:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:05:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      c1oPoE3LFCWAxNwCIOs8: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `gLc6pnoGLAiQnvqIB2NP`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:44:19 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:44:19 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      cA7KSHjlkEnI3mCWnJbn: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `YhEVB9rHOq2nqT2iL8FA`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:08:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:08:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      cCotpFPfN06h68abTwbv: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `YhY0J9F5ZgAFdP2hnB5r`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:38:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:38:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      cGdVE18rxLZnWGtaCBHI: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `VfgUBe5yEsbYhemZSPvY`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:16:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:16:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      cI1iI980bWzkjZG3oyUa: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `QdmlqU4NSFuH0HQkUVaN`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:17:23 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:17:23 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      cZA4W5bA6cPbePbIuRWm: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `Sp2DPRBhKZN3uxWBouxx`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:59:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:59:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      cntlu7mtMW82VYhaMhYh: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `84rD9t7GtDJdhYUFxjYI`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:08:13 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:08:13 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      cyzGGhaXOoWFKxdR3K83: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `O6nLHZq03gaIiNRYgmiW`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:14:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:14:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      d2tIAi7G9wx0b91yi19k: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `tkAVSNqo4N23uA7fCsA2`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:58:16 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:58:16 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      dSDJ6caommsfStWeq2xP: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `1ZtrgiGNeuUC1DkcNXcy`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:36:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:36:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      dkv4P3csG0fUIiwEV8bV: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `YwrPyowER19QAyxtRKmi`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:31:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:31:57 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      dvUkKYBychAAw0ghUjfz: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `pmNeGAno5dOwKYREyrdy`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:01:12 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:01:12 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      dwfcAoIOqYHfPJSt5hfh: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `dIJCKG95yobF3vv71OXP`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:36:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:36:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      e1Fei8AcBFkq3xMw4HbO: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `bBIsE26aKnYYa6tE3r6j`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:20:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:20:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      e2cGw9Wpbw5TRqEHBbnk: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `0ezG10Nkobi5iSJEWf9d`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:36:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:36:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      eJvZVvLcvIXXyYJ3z1Wg: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `t2nwmmnrhXHVIaf4DCX2`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:44:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:44:30 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      enFmQCSglqROiuhnU3F4: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `tEVwM6GmpSjXx1cUjluc`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:06:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:06:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      esqitUgVtbOjeQ7ACVzj: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `kpVRIsGQOEx1M2GvTV8P`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:43:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:43:47 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      exKDZW5nBCH2yUwHQf7y: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `MS3WqxgUYHk8fVoOwxwA`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:55:15 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:55:15 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      f0LWGv2YiY3uOfkCV8N7: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `xsJ8a9sbXMnrfWQxuMsE`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:09:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:09:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      f9wXsYXjR2Pr8D1ydake: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `gnIvZuRIrotwS0vG1AWB`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:45:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:45:08 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      fBddrpXVnj6B4WSREkR1: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `o3w4uHnVjQPn9XtjoEtb`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:00:23 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:00:23 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      g2vlRsaEnvqIwUluxNIf: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `k75lJV7p4ULqBp9CFt4o`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:22:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:22:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      g8l1BmHMhkutfZ6jIDCU: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `D0ef86druiWAKOyy5GpV`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:51:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:51:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      gkbymSdverDkDIIJMoeK: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `ca5u1TfScGvX8p1rt2xR`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:35:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:35:31 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      hGLcHeRw9iyw2xsG77EX: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `cBJUbcDpc0KFa9leAyF3`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:35:15 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:35:15 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      hGZuE65688iY8TaQZdRv: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `JwptsWGVv982Nyh56VYR`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:54:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:54:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      hKcAgYMlmUiuj3UfIeWT: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `cKYQEIb3YdAVmIMraSCY`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:20:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:20:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      hU337FM2Co3VKMQ4yYO5: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `tNmwfxT5tfjeOJcec5Ox`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:06:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:06:40 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      hVSQZ0doo9ZU0dYyfRuv: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `P1qrYCABgtWc8WmDQbjp`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:58:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:58:42 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      hzSiISz6cimJAmbk2myr: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `37woBGMH0WQiLuS5BAeS`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:38:12 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:38:12 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      iEF7u2w5jA4xBU3PwlEu: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `gSlCxWsJ2dCeXeJXsOXs`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:42:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:42:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ijqc9tW2TKtGpCPu8BDS: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `OAuqM10ernyQLuzHbzEY`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:11:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:11:29 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ioBfY2fNrRpe6HmYgWLD: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `psjf7v53HTUMBTGTjqrK`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:03:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:03:00 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      jO7iQmAbCFs7iZ8gOnRq: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `TRwfYZnGqgKLuZxqZoHK`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:27:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:27:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      jPXNFrJA6wyXYKhHPOAV: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `sQxbhYdrDa5lCIcScHcB`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:04:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:04:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      jYV4YZLzI6BNkYIuwYpr: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `1iotsUtcZbEkdZC5gevq`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:37:16 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:37:16 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      jmGTvT3DT45b6LLyUtNF: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `z1AA8bgTqN0tssfjHQEZ`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:10:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:10:49 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      kGOAzxipUtQux3sByg8u: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `eIBjL2u7DSNunxADWmRp`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:43:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:43:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      kRSI2RonO5xTujmmE9ng: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `rdcJ1YUPhXvBpIDCA1u6`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:03:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:03:50 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      kejh0HiT1Oujxls109CW: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `OOtEOgPKpb0u66ZP3i2e`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:57:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:57:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      kh5bc6ix0liVR1cBiuve: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `P1VjsuSnwSxRy27H3J5D`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:16:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:16:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      khQ3traKolz2lvF3NMa2: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `kMsqSvD04yI2SUoQcuwZ`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:52:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:52:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      kkkDTzsLGuAWT3joTORr: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `NpBvvQfmrYqyQSj4P8Jj`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:14:15 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:14:15 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      kxZwoPewuGhKfb0sBqR0: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `jHIpx5SOdGlOTFc4H9oS`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:51:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:51:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      l48bSjuP0b2Fyt0A7ipp: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `wYPLTfePUOXk1kR85d48`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:58:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:58:45 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      l6mrnYeRGKaAkqC5L8NG: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `0ezG10Nkobi5iSJEWf9d`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 10:48:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 10:48:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      lWVCjCdcXMsLOu3OQIFF: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `dgsZE7Py3YEphKD4om3i`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:38:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:38:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      lgu1YFnfNMtyT11FBqQs: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `7qPc3dd4y6YldEVfagwp`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:47:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:47:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      lmNxi0iAU12tpfEFI8xg: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `D2VHesWO0RtfA56V1oHp`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:12:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:12:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      mA0rp9Lu7uIhwf9rj9Ly: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `WMAMBtfWj7fHj4ayIAFM`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:28:15 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:28:15 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      mN2d6UTR68zD6CaEAusv: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `6CTNUQxAEPaePDMxb9Fs`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:18:12 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:18:12 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      nJdI04mKqgtiGDPlsKih: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `QeOZCrvGt8GaYIEcu6Cc`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:19:07 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jun 14 2022 16:19:07 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      nKcj8nTgAB1ipptjrPoT: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `9SGpJPtKkmsHGXdCDhhM`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:48:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:48:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      nTpFfNYWFJpcug2QrAl7: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `Od3Y1LmcWzp8iW3DFi6b`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:15:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:15:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      nVVq4vDRGYG7GKn9KXPC: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `yKS4dVRGsi5yMujdn0eI`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:10:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:10:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      nWGWPPHVT0oG51hEXWcD: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `wVLaiyaTxT7aoT0lBEKv`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:07:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:07:43 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ngtfutcW3kHW85L1tpIE: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `shRkM395w8t6t3mEuIym`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:05:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:05:59 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      oRpya4Y3vY32nOHxQpLu: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `P4nhKmlBhcClOziyWv9p`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:17:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:17:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      odR7t19bY8TQOCZDLgb1: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `SXVLqruVrfiPRtRJhFs5`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:24:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:24:51 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      oeGYMCHJYxVpLw31d6jG: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `OizbC1Wy5b6P1aQO8r2J`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:16:10 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:16:10 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      oiX6zcCaC1UhOFtlTyOg: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `EgLGTdOOylCs761BWShw`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:50:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:50:37 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      plnjDvYa8Z6zJOREoLIy: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `8I6ov72gP3pnjodpTR1Q`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:47:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:47:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      q407CGIk1iUSBRujVwhO: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `604OztA7sPg45ngiLvnv`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:39:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:39:36 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      q4ikxnI64lPcvCOp3sda: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `RnYBVBRV6uR5qPfKZMB1`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:16:18 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:16:18 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      q6XYJmNvsgY9L8SpqdCy: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `nc1pIsz8qSdJafKPxu0c`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:58:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:58:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      q6tBtW5rF3rcVhmDNQXU: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `owTjsdhFmZxzR7b2BYhM`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:00:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:00:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      qB3LfeIgLJSw2Wgj8BUD: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `65d4eiB5gj3tqzADjZLS`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:45:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:45:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      qH7rie31AQ5OlBCo71r3: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `ir4as8XMJuCBrRgYgz0e`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:46:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:46:53 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      rXGNLaJ81FSIKTPnWPaq: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `pxyKVv75XvxkI0On6WwC`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:56:05 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:56:05 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      rYiOX4YCvHaMhKYcCVPq: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `x2JDJHZl5o4Mv8ufDpuZ`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:59:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:59:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      roXdQpv6TYUm9zXsIX8R: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `aoC7R7ILT3czQqC1yGni`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:32:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:32:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      rqhCikNU7L4E6oDBo95N: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `k8uX4t7uqxKPaIsqGB2I`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:43:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:43:39 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ryAfkWbaWNRg6uAFS3Zg: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `kj4RQMGvbkX9VcB34Oiq`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:53:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:53:27 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      s8rIsEL5azulxW07DlVF: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `2Sp0I2rRBEKbm7915fpD`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:07:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:07:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      sERgRyW66XhYzFfCRDYl: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `4rOkDl7D3ssN2d8sCuwv`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:38:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:38:34 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      sGyJbKNQs8ICfOKWdUrk: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `ebAYzDWzpvf3TonlEVGd`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:40:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:40:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      sheL8Sm8m1GW1XoGMH6g: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `cvxoITdED8intcJG1Hik`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:36:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:36:26 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      soDbB3hAXKeWzJM37KuT: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `nuV9Fgg95gqKn3nAK5aY`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:55:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:55:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      tPDom6DIfdMvU6jFAs0V: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `TyGvI6tWM7Pu47os7Jev`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:03:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:03:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ty20lA8FxtLieKWsS0k4: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `I5Q4NmNvHt5UaL9zRhpX`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:52:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:52:38 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      uJk3Jz8rvrgXCiOJCaMf: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `z7CyCCTXXILXJDnLgg5X`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:23:54 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      uQBemSubLxPJvKDB0X5x: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `nzjFDGQSfuMQ5RWpKodM`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:44:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:44:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      uju1OQce04GwFWot0hwX: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `7bORBqVlHQw5vDTnp03R`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:46:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:46:58 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      v4r0kgX6shHL2zHIgvIN: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `7cnpslax9ultB1HDMdSp`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:47:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:47:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      vPFyubet8qDe0vrXmwZO: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `HcmqfnXyxCvqDEZW3sh5`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:12:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:12:52 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      vyShovKTUEBijIzUo9xP: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `tqV9ty0Q59tobpjUzDMf`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:23:22 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 10:23:22 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      w33ngTWiZsIOfgKPGiMp: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `nNV0excQLFKwnyOtI2rf`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:58:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:58:04 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      w4uTVsgR6BVJCedUWBPO: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `XwX02B0PNFzGMNAsRT9a`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:29:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:29:55 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      wVsuDGjU20TfNLgsB1h9: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `qdTZrxxCNFV9RMLpHs0e`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:03:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:03:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      wrrmr2PHNciWdMImQlNG: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `sfWxQEEmVBDKcALiLsXW`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:57:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:57:48 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      x70Ujfro7bJtGjOi0TwI: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `hiIJdO2jHamImbeay4rm`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:44:11 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 13 2022 09:44:11 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      xA4DlxocEFDDGBq8O1uQ: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `sGuZBEwJ34A84KnV18Ic`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:56:24 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 11:56:24 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      xWADRTiRUOxaLq77hoQl: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `gWfgyjOWqPVme9PZrc3Z`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:44:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:44:46 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      xXdnQC626nd8hdhWqHmF: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `S3PkvcUQLLgAr45l6IN3`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:18:22 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:18:22 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      xbmC3m27c6lKbseLsmlt: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `kySEs66HyxbkU5PzUmyP`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:54:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:54:02 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      ySNlZuiqWW80Osj3kiPw: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `XW0ceoyPz8kkWJ9dZ9qn`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:29:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:29:25 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      yWcxIAb2KhIeKQDNMNH0: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `NBAtwIbueE0ToJq1UdOO`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:10:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:10:28 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      yr2VwxKpJoGP1jdjzO0V: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `CjX10rm5OcsWh6KS5Ol4`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:11:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jul 06 2022 09:11:09 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      yywhmGWkLtYYsi0xH8eH: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `wmX3eDhft1rztxTyHCUN`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:08:22 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:08:22 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      zJNwCQ7qQR1V1Xtyv3D6: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `ypL5qxLQSj2lZMgK0kLM`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:10:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 12:10:41 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      zdosRd2FxTYBP3Op1bKl: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `F1rdp3F63qzbHezCGw05`,
        createdDate: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:51:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Wed Jun 15 2022 10:51:33 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      zkvS9RRfojJ4V56TetWQ: {
        result: `GOOD`,
        memoryId: `S47Vmz0uVWY3PC5A5hg9`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:18:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 11:18:35 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
      znxPcXoPh0dR6vUCsIKm: {
        result: `BAD`,
        memoryId: `5hrsF5NQEU6Dgh2eCC1f`,
        createdDate: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:39:06 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
        lastModified: `Tue Jul 12 2022 10:39:06 GMT-0400 (Eastern Daylight Time)`,
      },
    },
  },
  layout: { isDrawerOpen: true },
};
